Ja-eun, you answer.
Do you want to stay as an F?
No.
I don't.
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
You heard her.
Now beat it.
You rich, pretty,
and manipulative bully.
A bully?
If I'm a bully,
I wonder what you are, Ja-eun.
I've been thinking
why do you suddenly have hope?
It's okay though.
I'll snuff it out of you soon.
It was Ha-rin, right? She's the
one who dropped our rank.
What about Wu-ie then?
Is she out?
I don't know.
Hell, are you okay with this?
If Ha-rin turns on us...
If my dad finds out...
Shit.
Ye-rim.
I'm sorry!
Are you in love with me?
For real?
I thought it was just a joke
common in girls' high schools.
Listen carefully, Eun-jeong.
If my debut falls through
because of your stupid crush...
That's not going to happen!
You'll get to debut.
PYRAMID GAME
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON THE WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
EPISODE 6
We need to get more
people on our side.
Not with threats like last time,
but like how you
persuaded Jae-hyeong.
We can't be like Ha-rin.
We have to be more like you.
Like Ja-eun...
What would you do?
What?
Seung-ie.
About what happened...
Huh?
If you really felt hurt
because of me,
I'm sorry.
I mean it.
Oh?
Okay...
-Thanks for accepting my apology.
-I'm really sorry again.
You did good.
Hi, Ji-ae.
-What?
-You're friends with Ji-ae?
No, I just said hi.
I'm allowed to say hi, aren't I?
Fs
don't exist anymore.
On that note,
I'm thinking about doing away
with the game altogether.
What do you think, Ha-rin?
You always win by
a landslide anyway.
21 votes.
At the very top,
even among the As.
The person who'll be the sorriest
to see the Pyramid Game go
would be you.
Oh, that's right.
You said you were just one
of the 25 girls in this class.
Then if everyone agrees,
I guess it won't matter.
Right?
-Are you nuts?
-Seong Su-ji, you bitch!
Give a little warning before
you go off like that, Wu-ie.
What if you scare Ha-rin again?
Let me know if you agree
either by social media or text.
Anytime.
Oh, Ha-rin. You too.
She crushed it! Woo!
Ja-eun, hi!
I'm sorry.
I mean it.
Huh?
Hi, Ji-ae.
Ja-eun, hi!
I'm thinking about doing away
with the game altogether.
You said you were just one
of the 25 girls in this class.
You want the data
on who voted for whom?
Why?
Just because.
Da-yeon, let's go get
some snacks. On me.
Do-ah, you wanna go?
What are you staring at?
Do-ah, Da-yeon, Wu-ie.
Their long-term rule is over.
Seol-ha may have looked like
she was part of the group,
but she was never on
Ha-rin's good side.
But how on earth
did Eun-byeol become an A?
Do-ah, Da-yeon,
if you're going to get snacks,
bring me some chocolate milk.
I get low on sugar after calculus.
-What?
-Didn't you hear me?
Chocolate milk.
Get me some.
Oh, Ha-rin is here.
Ye-rim, Ha-rin,
you guys want anything?
We can ask them to get it for us.
Is that really Eun-byeol?
Maybe she had an evil twin?
She came to school
with an entirely different soul.
Her grades may been 2nd in our
year, but she was a total loser!
Eun-byeol
must've been Ha-rin's hidden card
from the start.
Ha-rin, I was waiting for you.
Anything you want me
to do today?
I need to talk to you.
Good.
Here, your reward.
Thanks.
JUNIOR YEAR PHYSICS
MIDTERM FOR SECOND SEMESTER
Come to the Director's office
at lunchtime tomorrow.
Eun-byeol.
Do you feel a little better?
Do-ah and Da-yeon...
Your sidekicks dropped to a B.
Do-ah deserved it
but Ye-rim replacing Da-yeon
wasn't the plan.
That means the morons
in our class voted for her.
This is so annoying!
Still, you don't have to worry.
I'll do whatever you want me to.
Just help me out
during the finals too.
So, these are
the final members?
Ye-rim instead of Ji-ae?
A loser is out, and a star is in.
Oops.
Don't say that.
I was just kidding.
This is Ye-rim.
She's popular in the class
and an idol trainee.
She has as much influence
as Ha-rin over the girls.
Wait, you're Wu-ri's brother?
Sorry, Ye-rim.
He already got that
reaction from us.
Really?
How is Wu-ri?
She turned into a hikikomori.
Were you a part of it?
Yes, I was a bystander.
I don't want to be this time.
So, Su-ji?
Did anyone reach out?
Of course
not.
They have no reason
to bet on us. Yet.
Then, what's our next plan?
We have to turn the princess
into a commoner.
First thing to do,
bring Ha-rin down.
CLEANING IS EVERYONE'S JOB
Ha-rin!
Where are you going?
You're in charge of
cleaning the classroom.
Eun-byeol, the room
on the 2nd floor.
What?
Ha-rin never cleans.
Huh? Why not?
We're all equals here, aren't we?
Su-ji,
we're As.
Oh...
Ye-rim, you have to help.
So?
Ye-rim is an A too.
But she's cleaning.
Sure I am.
Eun-byeol, does this annoy you?
Ugh, I can't do this.
It's not even trendy anymore.
That's enough.
You think you've
become something
because Ye-rim
is taking your side?
Damn it.
What did you just say to me?
Watch it. You're in no position
to be violent.
Also, what's the big deal
about cleaning?
Ha-rin, you didn't
start this, did you?
Is holding a broom too
lowly a job for an A?
You're going to skip cleaning?
Wow, that would
really suck, right?
Yeah, a lot.
You can get more brooms
from the teacher's office.
Thanks.
You can't?
Did you think
I was asking for a favor?
Thanks for this.
But I'm a techie,
not someone who uses tech
to do someone else's bidding.
That would be an insult
to the app I created.
Also, I got a D
again in this game
with only one vote.
You think I care?
You're all so stupid.
What the...
She's insane. Does she
know how much this costs?
Seriously!
BAEK HA-RIN HAS SENT $4,840 SENDER
MAY CANCEL BEFORE YOU ACCEPT
What a bitch.
It's Jae-hyeong.
Hey, what happened to you?
Did Ha-rin do this to you?
No, there was a leak
under the sink...
Huh?
My sink broke down
and I was trying to fix it.
Oh...
You're really coming over?
Why? You don't want me to?
It's not that.
It's just a really old house.
Let's go.
Aren't we going in?
You said your sink needs fixing.
Yeah.
There.
Here.
Clean your hands.
Okay.
Thanks. Tomorrow, I'll...
I'll buy you ma-malatang.
Do you have any ramyeon at home?
Ramyeon?
You want to eat
here before you go?
Yes.
Oh...
That hurts.
Jae-hyeong says
this ramyeon is
super popular these days.
If you don't like it,
I got cheese ramyeon,
or fish cake ramyeon,
or tteok ramyeon.
If you like dumpling ramyeon,
I got dumplings
so you can make that if you want.
What is all this?
Why'd you buy so much?
I didn't know what you liked...
You want some rabokki?
Dig in.
You can cook too?
Just a few things.
The gate creaking...
Get some lubricant spray.
-Lubricant...
-Spray.
Oh, okay.
How do you know so much?
You even fixed the sink.
I just look things up on YouTube
to solve things on my own.
Since I don't have a mom.
Sorry.
Is that your mom in the photo?
You said she didn't live here?
Yeah.
She moved to Busan
after my dad died last year.
I'm going to
live there too one day.
I want to farm
and help out with the orchard.
She wants me to become
a civil servant though.
What do you want to be?
A building owner.
Job-wise... I want to be
a documentary producer.
I think you'll be good at anything
since you get good grades.
Sorry.
Is it Jae-hyeong again?
HA-RIN
NEW MESSAGE
COME OUT. NOW
How long
have you known Ha-rin?
Seems like you go way back.
In elementary school...
We were in the same class
until she transferred out.
Dig in.
Have you
heard of Madagascar?
My mom is on a
business trip there.
She goes to Italy,
and the U.S. too.
My dad works at
a big company in Seoul.
You know Baekyeon Group, right?
It's the biggest company
in the country.
Anyway, I used up all my
allowance to buy a Nintendo.
I'll buy next time, Ja-eun.
Thanks.
I'm sorry
but I'm not an F anymore.
MYEONG JA-EUN
No one has reached out yet?
Not yet.
For the next part of the plan,
we need to spread a rumor.
A rumor?
Wait,
-where's Ja-eun?
-We have to start without her
because this rumor is about her.
Jae-hyeong, this is your
area of expertise, right?
Nope!
Just one of many.
This isn't a betrayal, is it?
You heard about Ja-eun?
I feel kind of bad.
I thought she became an F because
she was so gloomy and creepy.
But turns out she was betrayed.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Yeon-du sprayed it all over me.
Ja-eun! Over here.
Ye-rim, what are you doing?
You've never talked to Ja-eun
before, have you?
We're all in the same class.
It'd be nice to be friends.
Ha-rin, your goal is to
make Ja-eun the F permanently,
but mine is the exact opposite.
We'll be summarizing
the composers and their works
in the Romantic Era.
One of the main composers
was Schubert.
Hey.
Doesn't Ja-eun seem more
ordinary than you think?
She's pretty nice.
Who the hell betrayed her?
I know.
It's one of us.
If it were me,
I'd want to die about now.
Seong-ah,
I'm on duty today.
Can you take this
to the teacher's office for me?
Me?
-Why?
-You only got one vote.
I'll take it. I'm really strong.
Huh?
But you got more than one vote.
We're all friends here.
Wow, so nice.
Why was she ever an F?
Come to think of it,
ever since she started voting,
Ja-eun has never been the F.
She just rejected playing the game
because she didn't like it?
That's so cool.
See how she helped
Seong-ah just now.
Ja-eun is so cool.
GREAT JOB, GUYS
THE SECOND STAGE IS GOING TO PLAN
For the third stage,
we have to change the rules.
I'll tell you on Monday...
-Hi, Dad.
-Going out?
To the convenience store.
I'll be right back.
I've been reassigned again.
I have to start work in Paju
starting next month.
Get ready to transfer schools.
What?
30 people were trapped
in a warehouse fire
in Gyeonggi-do...
There has been no
contact for 7 hours.
The building...
Out of those 30 people...
If you were the only one
who could be rescued,
what would you do?
People instinctively
want to survive, don't they?
I'd live,
and live with the guilt.
What?
No way.
They're all different.
I like this one.
Things can go back
to the way it was.
I can get out of here.
See you.
Alone.
Tell the school
about your transfer this week.
THE GIRLS
Should we go ahead
with Stage 3 today?
TELL THE SCHOOL
ABOUT YOUR TRANSFER THIS WEEK
Yes.
Ye-rim, why don't you
take point on this one?
I'll support from behind.
I was thinking...
If we don't get an F
in the next game either,
why don't we get rid of
the As' benefits too?
If there's no lower rank
to mess around with,
there's no point in being As.
Also, Da-yeon, Wu-i, and Seol-ha,
you should apologize to Ja-eun.
I heard you broke the rules.
"Leave no trace no matter what."
Did you forget?
What?
-I didn't do anything.
-Don't deny it.
There was a witness.
I saw everything.
On August 31st,
after 4th period PE.
In the gym closet.
You guys beat her up until
she was black and blue.
We didn't.
Then, can the three of you
say where you were
and what you were doing on
that day at the same time?
Ye-rim.
There will be an F
in the next game.
Based on what?
We didn't have one this time.
So, you're against it, right?
Then, should we vote on it?
Okay.
Let's do that.
If we don't get an
F in the next game,
the As will lose
their benefits too.
Even if I'm not around,
things have started to change.
It won't be like before.
Are you not feeling well?
You look like you've lost weight.
MOM
Is it just the screen?
What about dinner?
What did you eat?
I'm not sick.
I had some ramyeon
with friends earlier.
Ramyeon?
You should eat a proper meal!
What about you?
I ate too.
Ramyeon.
By the way, Ja-eun.
So-eun came by yesterday.
-Kim Da-yeon.
-Here.
-Cho Mi-yeong.
-Ra Hae-jun.
-Here.
Myeong Ja-eun.
She's absent again?
For two days in a row
without any notice?
Mr. Im, Ha-rin isn't here either.
She requested
a field trip today.
That'll be all.
First period is music.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
MYEONG JA-EUN
Still not answering?
She hasn't been
taking my calls since yesterday.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
I'll talk to the school
about my transfer in a few days.
MYEONG JA-EUN
I was wondering why you
took me to the department store.
Be honest with me.
Where did you get
all those gift certificates?
We'll talk inside.
I'm so happy.
I live downstairs, Lieutenant
Colonel Seong Hee-seok...
Oh, you brought us
the plant last time.
Are you coming back
from after-school classes?
Yes, do you need any help?
You have a lot to carry.
Oh, you really don't have to,
but thank you.
HONG SANG-GU
LIEUTENANT COLONEL SEONG HEE-SEOK
TRANSFERRED TO INFANTRY UNIT 0663
COLONEL HONG SANG-GU
HONG SANG-GU
There will be an F
in the next game.
But why am I the only one
rescued of all people?
You want to turn a blind eye?
You think it's a coincidence?
Transfer? All of a sudden?
I know it's sudden.
I wasn't expecting this either.
I thought you'd be
able to graduate
from your current school.
BAEK HA-RIN
This is Su-ji.
Su-ji?
I don't know what this is about,
but I'm a little busy right now.
SEONG SU-JI
SOS.
Did you want to call out for help?
Oh well.
It's just the two of us here.
It was a popular song back then.
Do you remember?
You always forget everything
so easily.
I haven't forgotten a thing.
Does your mom know?
Why I'm
tormenting you so much.
You can tell her.
What I did was wrong.
Can I tell your new friends too?
You know about this place?
It's no coincidence.
-Isn't that right?
-What?
Don't play dumb.
You used your rich
parents' connections
so that I wouldn't
get in your way anymore.
I'm telling you now, I'm not
transferring to a new school.
You can't get rid of me.
A new school?
I thought you'd be happy.
I would've been.
Because
Su-ji, the Pyramid Game
will never end.
It can't, because of Ja-eun.
Can you anticipate
how far I'll go?
I can't.
Run. Now's your chance.
You're a psycho.
You're really going
to destroy the game?
No.
I'm going to
destroy you too
for the game to be truly over.
You are the Pyramid Game.
But...
Why are you trembling
so much, Su-ji?
Were you waiting for me?
Since when?
Why didn't you call?
I dropped my phone a few
days ago and it broke.
I didn't wait that long.
Why did you miss out on school?
I had a cold.
I had something to tell
you and the others
once we got rid of the game.
Will you be here
until then?
Dad, I'm not changing schools.
I'm going to graduate from here.
If that's what want,
then alright. You do that.
Let's go.
Mr. Im is going to
give you an earful
for missing school
without any notice.
I know.
I shouldn't have.
Before we go, let's drop
by the convenience store.
Hello.
Do you have the recordings?
We have quite a lot now.
Evidence we collected.
How are you going to release it?
With a YouTube account
from another country.
It can't be traced that way.
I'm going to break it
wide open soon.
Class 2-5's
Pyramid Game...
-You bitch.
-I'll crush you.
Have you been curious?
You psycho!
You bitch!
-You were an F...
-Shit.
There will be
an F in the next game.
I made a short, shocking version.
It'll get more hits
based on the algorithm.
But...
once this gets released
you could end up like my sister.
I'm exposing this
so that it won't happen.
Politicians' children, national
team athletes, celebrities...
Do you know what
they're most afraid of?
Tip-offs.
Tip-offs from the public.
How lucky are we
that Baek Ha-rin is from
a major conglomerate family.
Hey, it's Ja-eun.
She came to school today.
-Hi, Ja-eun.
-Hi.
Ha-rin, we're friends.
If you don't like something
about me, I'll change.
I'll change everything.
I won't bother you either.
Really. I promise.
Tell her.
What I did was wrong.
Ja-eun too!
I'll mess her up good.
I'll totally kill her.
Friends?
Wu-ie.
I don't treat my friends
this way.
Stop being funny
and get out.
Hey, Do-ah.
You too.
Ha-rin and I have a lot to
talk about with Da-yeon.
Wow, it's so soft.
How much does something
like this cost?
It must be expensive.
By the way,
did you like the photo?
I was wondering if
I got a good shot.
Yes.
-I like it.
-I'm glad.
Also, I think we need
to tighten control
on the morons in our class.
No matter how much
they get their hopes up,
the game will never stop, ever.
Should we go with that concept?
Sure.
Let's do it during PE.
I'll arrange it.
What is she, five?
This is so stupid.
What are you doing here?
Our phones must've
gotten switched earlier.
Do-ah.
The ballet studio at lunch.
Ballet studio?
Baek Ha-rin's group?
Oh...
Do-ah, you're back
to being cute again.
There's nothing useful.
It's okay.
We have enough.
-Dinner?
-Yes.
My sister used to have that
exact same look on her face.
Guess when?
When she'd come home
alone late at night.
Whatever.
Ha-rin, let's go.
Today's class is going to be fun.
You can look forward to it.
The performance test
for the PE final
is being replaced with dodgeball.
Target dodgeball.
Target dodgeball?
What's that?
This is the performance test?
FYI, the teacher has to work
on a trip itinerary
and won't be here.
But don't worry.
Our class rep will be
keeping score.
The rules are simple.
Within
a time limit of 20 minutes,
those who earn six points
will get a perfect score
in the performance test.
If not, you get a zero.
You'll be graded
according to your scores.
You score by hitting the target.
To be more exact, the four Ds
who only got one vote each
in the Pyramid Game.
The performance test
is a group assault?
How can they be so shameless?
Target?
Why the Ds with only
one vote all of a sudden?
The rank to replace the F.
Without an F...
The fear that Ds could
end up like the F.
Get six points within 20 minutes.
A mission, limitations,
and an individual match...
This trio makes people
do crazy things.
They'll do anything to attack
anyone weaker than themselves.
Once they get into it,
they'll never be free
of the game.
Interesting.
Time out.
Why is our performance
test target dodgeball?
Was it the teacher's decision?
Of course not.
She said she'd leave it up to us,
so me and Ha-rin decided.
Why?
Because you two are As?
Wow, I'm so hurt.
I'm an A too.
Do you have
another idea?
I do.
The target.
We should include all the Ds.
SUGGEST MAKING ALL DS THE
TARGET 1 POINT IF YOU HIT A D
3 POINTS IF YOU
HIT DS WITH ONE VOTE
One point if you hit a D.
Three points if you hit a D
with one vote.
What?
Why?
What are you doing, Ye-rim?
Why us...
There are 12 Ds
who got more than two votes.
That's too much.
I can't let those 12 target
the weak who only got one vote.
That's what Ha-rin wants.
She's trying to stop the
group assault on the one votes?
Not that it'll do any good.
What should we do?
It's hard to say no
to an A.
That's exactly why
Su-ji is putting Ye-rim forward.
Fine.
Three balls
will be used to play.
As, Bs, Cs,
Ds, then Ds with one vote
will stand in the circle
in that order.
If you step on the line,
it'll be minus two points.
Should we begin?
PE FINAL, PERFORMANCE TEST SCORES
GU SEOL-HA +3
JEONG YEON-DU +1
Five minutes before total chaos.
Shit!
Throw it!
Damn it, let go!
Let go!
Pandemonium.
This is exactly what
you wanted, right?
Geez, dumb athlete.
So annoying.
Maybe we shouldn't have allowed
the one votes to touch the ball.
We're all in this game together.
Eun-jeong is doing her part.
Oh, inducing anger.
Damn you, Ji-ae.
Stop throwing it to Eun-jeong,
you dummy.
Ow, shit.
The climax.
Ja-eun, minus two points.
Hey, pass the ball!
I only have three points!
Shit!
Holding on to the ball
is a foul, isn't it?
First, take possession
of all the balls.
Then put the game on hold.
She wouldn't...
Well, Do-ah?
Record my three points.
SEONG SU-JI +3
Do-ah!
Why are you writing that down!
Don't tap them with the ball!
Hit them!
That wasn't part of the rules.
Three balls are used to play.
As, Bs, Cs, Ds,
then Ds with one vote
will stand in the
circle in that order.
Minus two points
if you step on the line.
Score six points
and you get a perfect grade
on the performance test.
Those were the rules.
Enough.
Shit!
Da-yeon, Ja-eun, one point.
Just now, Da-yeon
not only openly
rebelled against an A,
she turned everyone against her.
We have the upper hand now.
You want the ball?
Ja-eun, thanks for earlier.
Who does Da-yeon think she is?
She almost broke my bones.
When did the four of you
become friends though?
-Uh?
-Do you play any sports, Ja-eun?
Basketball? Volleyball?
No, I don't.
Are you really going
to get rid of the game?
Don't tell anyone
I reached out.
I'm really sorry,
Su-ji. I really am.
If I side with you guys,
it won't hurt me, will it?
Where's Ja-eun?
She's changing.
-And Ye-rim?
-She's changing too.
Three club sandwiches,
and one BLT salad to go, please.
All on honey oat bread
with all the veggies,
and your recommended sauce.
Got it.
Look, Su-ji.
I know you don't totally trust me,
but once I make a decision,
I don't go back on it.
I'm just saying.
When is Monsta X
making their comeback?
Next month!
I'm going to group
purchase their album.
You want in on it?
Who is your bias?
Hyung-won.
He's got the best body.
You perv.
Hyung-won has the best face.
-I see. You go for faces.
-Hmph.
Your sandwiches are ready.
I'm starving.
Let's eat here.
Good, right?
This combination is
the best of the best.
Yeah, it's good.
So, your bias is Hyung-won.
Who do you like next?
-Min-hyuk!
-Oh, Min-hyuk!
Wow, I don't believe this.
I've found my buddy.
Do you want to go to
M Countdown together?
No.
Come on, let's go!
If you go, I'll buy you a combo!
Wow, that was tougher
than dance practice.
It's going to go online tomorrow.
The evidence we recorded.
Tomorrow?
Oh, sorry.
I just thought of Ye-rim.
Did you see her face
when she caught the ball?
Even that face can
look a little ugly.
I've seen the possibilities.
Yeah, I'm human after all.
I agree.
-Su-ji, you looked like a squid.
-Shut up.
You two have become close.
You shut up too.
Don't be jealous, Ja-eun.
My bias is you now.
My number one pick
and bias wrecker.
I'm sorry.
I just lost it for a sec.
I'll make it up to you, Ha-rin.
This is Ha-rin.
Da-yeon just made a huge mistake.
She needs to be scolded, sir.
Here, it's your dad.
Hey...
What?
Go to the hospital.
For your ankle.
Dummy.
Click.
You two are still friends?
Keeping your distance
did seem to mean something.
So, to Eun-jeong,
Ye-rim and swimming still matter.
When's the competition?
Why? So you can
spread rumors before it starts?
That she likes girls?
Well, you can't.
If you do, I'm going to tell
everyone you're a psychopath.
Or are you going
to use your money?
Don't.
I have plenty of money too.
Why do you think my parents
never come on Parents' Day?
Because they don't need
to suck up to Baekyeon Group.
Your methods
won't work on me.
I heard your parents don't want
you to become an idol singer.
And that's why you're not
on good terms with them.
If your debut falls
through this time,
you won't get another
chance on your own.
Isn't that right?
-Right, Ye-rim?
-Damn you.
Give it your best shot.
What are you doing?
Get up.
Get up, now!
Get up!
Don't do this, Eun-jeong.
How touching.
I'll be keeping an eye
on you from now on.
Ye-rim. Don't make
Eun-jeong kneel again.
Damn you...
What is up
with that bitch, Ha-rin?
Now you ask?
I wasn't interested before.
There's another invisible
pyramid within the As.
This is Ha-rin.
Let's assume that out of the
21 girls who vote for Ha-rin,
nine vote for someone else,
and she loses her A status,
and this game stops.
If you multiply 1/2 nine times
over that comes to is 1/512.
Even if this game disappears
by a 1/512 chance,
the pyramid will still exist.
That's why we do
what Ha-rin says.
And that's why
I was relieved.
Do-ah, you're back
to being cute again.
It makes me sick.
How's Da-yeon?
Probably getting beat up.
Her dad is trash.
You bitch!
It's all your fault!
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-Sit up straight, damn it.
You're back.
Let me...
Why don't we send her abroad?
I'm sure my mother
would be okay
with sending her
to boarding school.
Your mother is not the problem.
Ha-rin has proof that
you laundered money
through the school's foundation.
What does my mother see in her...
She's a psychopath.
Even if she is our daughter.
Did you record
more evidence today?
This is my evidence.
The recordings?
How did she know?
I think I deserve to be back in.
Do-ah, you're back
to being cute again.
Seo Do-ah.
You didn't ignore it this time.
BAEKYEON GROUP'S MENTORING PLAN
What is that?
Baekyeon Group's PR team
contacted the unit.
The Chairman
seems to be interested
in social work.
If you release your evidence.
This is how I'll use mine.
LIEUTENANT COLONEL
SEONG OF UNIT 6694
USES HIGH SCHOOL DAUGHTER
TO FORM TIES WITH A CONGLOMERATE
MADE DAUGHTER TRANSFER SCHOOLS
TO MAKE A PERSONAL CONNECTION
LIEUTENANT COLONEL'S CORRUPTION
BEHIND MENTORING PROGRAM
CORRUPT LIEUTENANT COLONEL'S
PERSONAL INFO EXPOSED
There's more.
Can you anticipate
how far I'll go?
Why are you trembling, Su-ji?
Hey. Su-ji.
It hasn't expired yet.
What do you want to do?
You collected it, so you decide.
This is the recycle bin.
The reason I trembled
in front of Ha-rin that day...
You are
the Pyramid Game.
This was why.
DELETE
Because of fear.
PYRAMID GAME