We're doomed.
We're so screwed.
2023 MACBOOK PRO 16 INCH
LOWEST PRICE $4,840
TENDS TO COMPLY
WHEN IT'S TO HER BENEFIT
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
I should've realized sooner.
You look like
your plan has been exposed.
There was a leak.
SEONG SU-JI
Oh?
What are you two doing here?
Waiting for you.
-What?
-Ye-won told me.
Ye-won.
-Can you do me a favor?
-A favor?
What is it?
If Su-ji starts making you feel
uncomfortable, will you tell me?
I heard you were
making her feel uncomfortable.
She came to me
saying that you'd been asking
a lot of questions.
And that Ja-eun was suddenly
following her around.
The Ja-eun I know would
never do something like that.
Did you make her do it?
Oh, I just wanted to be
friends with Ye-won.
Ja-eun, you too?
Anyway, I hear you.
I made her uncomfortable.
I see...
I know you're behind this.
Su-ji.
Do you want to sit next to me?
I think I'd be a better friend
than Ja-eun.
All of a sudden?
No, thanks.
I like sitting in the back.
You do?
Oh well.
So, this is the real you?
The real Baek Ha-rin.
You smoke?
Yeah, there are no cameras here,
and no one comes back here either.
You don't want to be
friends with me, do you?
How much do you know
about Ja-eun?
What about Ji-ae?
Do you really believe they're
the girls you think they are?
What do you mean?
Oh, is this about when I said
I'd be hanging out with them?
That was a low point in my life.
Can you just forget it?
I'm a C now, so why should I?
So lame.
Can you put that out?
I hate second hand smoking.
And how exactly do
I think about them?
Dumb chess pieces
that move according to your plan.
I'm sure that's what you thought
about Ye-won too.
But you're wrong, Su-ji.
You'll find out soon enough.
PYRAMID GAME
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
15TH PYRAMID GAME D-14
WHAT? HA-RIN CAUGHT ON?
How much?
The entire plan?
What about me?
EPISODE 4
I don't know about you guys,
but if this goes
wrong for me, I'll die.
She doesn't know
anything specific.
Just that we've been
trying to approach Ye-won.
That's practically
the whole plan.
You acted like
you were so meticulous.
I'm totally
disappointed in you, Su-ji.
Oh no.
Now what?
I've reached my limit.
You're no longer Fs
so you don't know how I feel...
It's been going on for a year.
They instinctively know
that Ha-rin has more to offer
than we do.
What do we do now?
Do we just give up?
We have to come
up with another way.
How?
-Mr. Im.
-Yes?
I'd like to talk to
the girls in class five.
If that's alright...
Why?
Are they in trouble?
Oh, no. It's nothing like that.
They're teenage girls.
I thought they'd be
more comfortable
sharing things with
a female teacher...
The problem is
they share too much.
I cover up so much for them
but they can't even show
their appreciation.
Excuse me?
Hey, F!
Where do you think you're going?
-What do you want?
-I'm sorry.
Ji-ae.
I've been wanting to talk to you.
I know this is rough on you.
But what's going on
with you and Su-ji?
Even from a distance,
I can tell she's trouble.
You two and Ja-eun
aren't up to something, are you?
What do you care?
Also...
Don't badmouth my friend.
Wait, hang on.
Are you really on her side now?
Are you sure
you can trust her?
It's a vitamin.
-Do you want one?
-Huh? No...
I did what you asked.
To Ji-ae.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
A HACKER AND A CRACKER
FUTURE PROGRAMMER
LIVE THE WAY I WANT TO
Is the MacBook Pro that awesome
among computer nerds?
Is it the Holy Grail?
You're a computer nerd, right?
A programmer?
-Why do you ask?
-Because it ruined my plan.
So freaking annoying.
PYRAMID GAME
14TH GAME RESULTS
PYO JI-AE 0 VOTES
YOUNGER SISTER
What? You need something?
What's up?
Hey, Ye-rim. I entered a contest
sponsored by your foundation.
Could you maybe pull some strings?
Ha-rin, you know that
Ye-rim likes my paintings, right?
Hey, Bang Wu-ie.
I'm just kidding.
I know Ye-rim doesn't like
talking about her family.
I like that color on your lips.
I've never seen you
wearing make-up before.
-Damn it.
-Why'd that get on my lips?
Yeah.
I wonder why?
What? You want me
to get some on you too?
No.
Get over here!
Ye-rim!
Okay, fine, fine.
-Pucker your lips.
-Stop, stop, Ye-rim.
-Stop.
Oh, Ye-won!
New laptop?
I voted for you two.
Something I want?
Not really.
No, I have to be careful.
We're down one.
We need at least one
of them on our side.
No, not Seung-ie.
What about Cho Yu-rim?
What's wrong with her?
She ate two bowls.
Hey.
-What about you?
-Me too. Two bowls.
Let's share ice cream.
Damn it!
Hey, get your stomach
out of the way.
Is your body shaped like a
D because your rank is D?
Look at this belly fat.
It's disgusting.
Oh, sorry.
Fuck this.
Wu-ie, don't you think
you're being too harsh?
She bumped into you
by mistake.
Ha-jun,
did you forget my rank?
You're not an A.
And neither Shin-ye or I am an F
I'm just asking you
not to swear so much.
Yeah.
Why is discipline
getting so slack?
It's totally pissing me off.
Do you think my rank
is any different
from Da-yeon's or
Do-ah's? Fuck...
Ha-rin!
Hae-jun is right,
don't you think?
Be more careful, Wu-ie.
This isn't a good look for you.
What?
We used to be friends.
Cho Yu-rim and you?
Oh, yeah.
You two were the only
new girls when
junior year started.
Hey.
But you became an F
right away after that.
Then, Yu-rim betrayed you?
Oh my god.
Why did they suddenly
join this class?
It means that Ha-rin
chose them specifically.
But why?
Did you know Ha-rin before?
She handpicked everyone here.
I wonder why she chose you
and Yu-rim to be in this class...
Looking for someone?
Could it be... me?
I'm hurt, you know.
Are you avoiding me?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Da-yeon!
How much do you know
about Ja-eun?
9 YEARS AGO
Green light, red light.
Green light...
Better not let me catch you!
Do you have a fever?
What do you know about dating?
Hang on.
Send it to me.
Looks like
you're close with Seol-ha.
I'm closer with you.
My dad wants to invite you over.
Do you have time next week?
Sorry.
I'm busy that day.
-I didn't say which day.
-I know.
Let's go.
You return the bike.
What am I going to tell my dad?
Damn it.
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
I'm back.
SEOSIM HOSPITAL
So, did things get awkward
with Da-yeon's dad?
You know it's not just
about the school board.
You get to network
with Baekyeon Group.
He knows that
and that's why he's livid
thinking I took his spot.
How are things at school?
The class atmosphere has changed
ever since a new girl named Su-ji
transferred in.
Dr. Yang's daughter
is in your class, right?
Do you know what the difference
is between Dr. Yang and me?
He doesn't have a family business
to pass on to his children,
but I can pass on the ownership
of this hospital to you.
That makes us bourgeois.
Just because you live inside
the same castle
doesn't make
everyone an aristocrat.
There should be a distinction.
All you need to care
about is Ha-rin.
Don't worry.
We'll put Yu-rim on hold for now.
This is our new target.
-Hae-jun?
-Ra Hae-jun.
She acts like she traded votes
with the girls
she hangs out with,
but she didn't actually
vote for them.
Huh? Why not?
Why did you do it?
Insecurity? Anxiety?
She was probably worried that
her friends would
rank higher than her.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
I texted her.
Hae-jun will be in contact soon.
PARENTS' DAY DATE &amp; LOCATION
Parents's Day?
At our age? That's so lame.
Yeah,
they did it last year too.
I only have a mom
and she doesn't live in Seoul
so she can't come.
-What about you?
-Probably not.
-Both of them?
-I only have a dad.
Oh, more importantly,
getting to a higher
rank starts now.
We need more info on our next
targets, more than Hae-jun...
What are you guys
talking about?
I noticed Ji-ae
was crying alone in the restroom.
Su-ji.
What exactly is going
on in your class?
Let me help.
I think I'll be able to help you.
Let the adults handle it.
If a problem arises,
work it out and get through
it instead of trying to avoid it.
What can you do?
I'll notify the school,
and call for a meeting
of the anti-bullying committee.
The bullies will be punished
according to procedure...
Oh, I see.
I'll just handle it.
Thank you for your concern.
This is serious.
BULLYING CONTINUES
IF YOU LOOK AWAY
REPORT BULLYING 117
SUICIDE HOTLINE 1393
Another poster?
We'll have to put it up again.
What a pain.
I appreciate it, Ms. Yun.
This is the junior
teachers' office.
Oh, ma'am.
Seong Su-ji's guardian?
LIEUTENANT COLONEL
SEONG HEE-SEOK
1 COMPANY 1 UNIT
BAEKYEON GROUP'S MENTORING
PROGRAM FOR YOUNG SOLDIERS
This is Lieutenant Colonel
Seong Hee-seok of Unit 6694.
Is this Seong Su-ji's father?
And who am I speaking to?
I hope all is well
with your family.
I'm the principal
of Baekeon Girls' High School.
The principal?
I apologize for calling
out of the blue.
You've received the notice sent
from our school, right?
I would very much appreciate it
if you could attend.
BAEKEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
NOTICE FOR PARENTS' DAY
Pyo Ji-ae!
What were you thinking? Why are
you bringing a teacher into this?
Well...
-She came up to me and asked.
-Su-ji, just calm down...
You know the plan.
Do you want to ruin everything?
Are things even
going according to plan?
-What?
-If it is, just say so.
I've been wanting to ask anyway.
How can you be just
like the other kids?
Do you even care that
I'm being bullied?
-Did you?
-Su-ji.
I told you.
We've both been bullied
just as much as you have.
Is it so hard to just trust me
and wait?
Yes, it's hard!
I can't trust anyone,
and I hate being at school.
It feels like no one
is on my side.
I have nightmares
every day.
When I open my eyes in the
morning, I just want to die!
So?
Am I your mother?
Are we bots you
can vent feelings to?
Don't delude yourself.
The only thing we have
in common is our goal.
Even so, I trust you.
Why? Because you're
both so dependable?
No.
Because without trust,
the whole plan fails.
I figured you'd know that.
I...
am not like you.
I'm not as strong as you are
and I'm a coward.
I really thought
you were my friends.
That's why I feel so hurt,
because we're friends.
Friends?
You've been looking down
on us all this time.
What? When did I do that?
"You're an F.
You rank below us."
"Don't you remember?"
You're an F.
You rank below us.
Yeah, I'm sure you thought
it was okay back then.
It's what everyone was doing.
Is that why
you thought you could still
treat us like that?
If you really thought of
Ja-eun and me as your friends,
you would've apologized
for it first.
Let her go.
RA HAE-JUN
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you bullshitting me?
-Do you have proof that I did it?
-Yes, I do.
I'm sure your friends know
your handwriting.
I heard
you used to be a C before.
But you purposely
went down a rank
to hang out with your friends.
Your friends think you're loyal
and that you look out for them.
Why? It's okay for you to be a D,
but you don't want anyone else
other than you moving up a rank?
If you don't want your friends to
know that you betrayed them,
you better cooperate
with us, Hae-jun.
What are you staring at?
Hey! She's not an F anymore.
Watch it.
Ja-eun and I
aren't below you.
In fact, we're the ones
holding something over your head.
All I have to do
is vote for you guys
in the next game?
Ra Hae-jun is in.
The next target is
Song Jae-hyeong.
Great photo.
Look at these muscles.
I love it.
Was it fun leaving us behind?
-What?
-Bitch, let's just go.
Forget it.
We're not waiting.
Come on.
See you.
What's up with her?
Damn it, she's too
good for us now?
Hey.
What are they doing here?
It's them, right?
Your "friends" you used
to get into trouble with.
They were just in
the neighborhood.
Yeah right.
I heard them bothering you.
If you start
hanging out with them again,
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm not stupid.
What matters to me the most
right now is swimming and...
Me?
You're a good friend,
aren't you, Eun-jeong?
By the way,
have you seen this?
She implies that
she actually knows you.
You think she's one
of those obsessive fans?
Trainees don't have
obsessive fans.
Let's go.
Come on.
You need to stop this.
Please, Wu-ri.
What do you want me to do?
Get out!
Tell me, what can I do?
Ji-ae, hang in there.
It's all going to be okay soon.
Slowly, carefully.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
-Bye.
-Thanks for coming.
YE-RIM, WHAT ARE
YOU LOOKING AT? LOL
Forget it.
Just ignore it.
Oh?
That guy...
Are you okay?
What about?
Oh, Ji-ae?
I'll soothe things over.
Things will go according to plan.
Don't worry about it.
No, not Ji-ae.
-You looked hurt.
-Me?
I'm fine. I just lost it for a
sec because of her attitude.
If you say so.
Ji-ae is like
an whiny, immature little kid,
but she's not a bad person.
Humans usually act according
to the situation they're in.
She was just a bystander.
Like I was.
But not you.
The real game starts now
but what are we going to do
about Jae-hyeong and Yu-rim?
You don't happen to have
anything on Yu-rim...
Never mind.
Your wrist.
Did you really mean it?
You wanted to die?
I don't know.
It was that terrible for you,
but you still wanted
to help Ji-ae?
And you eventually agreed to
get Yu-rim involved in our plan.
Oh, I just remembered.
I was wondering where
I saw him before.
-Ja-eun, can you hear me?
-Yes.
-You're recording this, right?
Call the police right away
if anything happens.
You're Cho Wu-ri's brother,
aren't you?
What were you doing in here?
Seong Su-ji! Seong Su-ji!
Yes, I found it.
I left it in the restroom
of the new building.
Yes, goodbye.
Wait.
You're a hacker?
I read an article about
the "Data Monster."
KOREAN HACKER
"DATA MONSTER" RANKS 3RD
IN INTERNATIONAL HACKING CONTEST
Why did you come here?
To get something?
To steal something?
Did Wu-ri make you do this?
The Pyramid Game.
The one you play in class.
What is it exactly?
Su-ji!
That part-timer
at the convenience store.
I mean, Cho Wu-ri's brother.
Let's get him to help us.
What?
No way.
Getting Hae-jun to work with
us is nowhere near enough.
We don't even have any info
on Jae-hyeong or Yu-rim.
And we're running out of time
until the next game.
Still, it's too dangerous.
We don't know anything
about him.
I know him a bit.
Besides, you're supposed
to team up with people
who are in similar situations.
Not people like our
literature teacher.
People like you, me, Ji-ae
and that guy.
Remember how I said
Ye-won could help us get dirt?
Wu-ri's brother
could do it instead.
What do you know about Wu-ri?
Tell me everything.
CHO SEUNG-HWA
It's bullying, right?
That vote and those
rankings or whatever.
If you don't get any votes, you
become the target of bullying?
How is Wu-ri doing?
She hasn't left her
room for months.
Hikikomori.
The only thing I can tell you
is that Wu-ri is a victim.
You want to know
what happened to
your little sister, right?
How about we work together?
1. ENLISTMENT NOTICE FOR ACTIVE
DUTY CHO SEUNG-HWA
15TH PYRAMID GAME D-10
12 UNREAD MESSAGES
CONVENIENCE STORE
Is Song Jae-hyeong a perv?
A perv?
#GYM IDOLS # AWESOME MUSCLES
#GREAT BODS
What a great photo.
Look at his body. Oh my god.
One club and one Italian BMT
on wheat with all
the veggies, please.
You can choose the sauce.
Mm, this is good.
-Wanna split it?
-Sure.
This is good too.
Oh, right. Look.
What's this?
They're from Jae-hyeong's
photo album.
Photos she secretly took
of people who are buff and tough.
If anyone finds out, she's
done for. Let's use this.
Eat. Lunch time is almost over.
Huh? Oh.
Song Jae-hyeong.
-I'll talk to her.
-You think you can do it?
Yes, I'll try.
I feel bad about leaving
everything to you.
There was nothing particular
on Cho Yu-rim.
There is one thing.
Look.
It's the same exact
painting that Yu-rim won
an award for at school.
CHO YU-RIM
Woah, that was close.
Hey, Ha-rin.
Thanks.
I got the text yesterday.
Oh...
Any changes
regarding Cho Yu-rim?
ANY CHANGES
REGARDING CHO YU-RIM?
LEAVE OF ABSENCE POSTPONEMENT FORM
Looking good today.
Wow, all that sweat.
What do you want?
You're a fan
of Shownu X Hyungwon, right?
You want this?
No thanks.
According to experts,
Shownu and Hyungwon
both have great physique,
and have well developed biceps.
Uh...
Muscles are built up
through weight training.
There's something called BCAA.
Leucine, valine, isoleucine...
Ah...
-Did you see?
-No.
You saw.
No.
Wouldn't it be better to ask
if it's okay to take
their photos first?
Portrait rights and all...
Hmph.
Mm, nice.
Why are you following me around?
If you're alone...
You might like a perv.
Wow.
She's not around this time?
Well, better for me.
Let's get some good shots.
What are you doing?
Were you taking photos of us?
No, I was taking a selfie.
I'll have her delete them.
I'm sorry.
She probably didn't mean
to take them.
Sorry, I overslept.
You...
I told you to come out.
Stop talking.
You're a F.
The lowest of the low.
Know your place.
Let's get it together, okay?
CLASS MOTTO HAPPINESS
FOR EVERYONE, A CLASS FOR ALL
Ji-ae, do better.
I'll be watching you.
CONVENIENCE STORE
NEW MESSAGE
Ji-ae, are you okay?
Yu-rim was selected
for a scholarship
by Baekyeon Art yesterday.
Ha-rin must be behind it.
Ha-rin?
I wonder how much
she knows about our plan...
Ji-ae, about what I said
the other day...
Oh.
You were right.
I was wrong.
I guess this means
we have to recruit
Seung-ie instead of Yu-rim?
-To the alliance of the Ds.
-Will you be okay with it?
It doesn't matter.
This easily?
The smell of cigarettes.
What?
Nothing.
How's it going with Jae-hyeong?
I've gotten a lot closer but...
Don't tell me
you haven't used that photo.
It's the easier and surest way.
I'm not as good as you at that.
-I'm doing it my own way for now.
-Your way?
The Ds...
-This is Baek Ha-rin?
-Yeah.
She just looks like a normal
higher school girl.
I've done some searching
but there are no photos
of her online.
The company must keep things
under tight control.
There's hardly
any info on her either.
Just a rumor that her
grandmother the Chairman is
wrapped around her finger.
Who should I look into next?
Joo Seung-ie.
This girl here.
DAD
Hello?
I won't be able to
make it home today.
-Did you eat?
-I ate and cleaned up.
I'll lock the doors and check
the gas before going to bed.
I heard that it's Parents' Day
at your school tomorrow.
Oh, you don't have to come.
It's not mandatory.
Okay then.
Good night.
SEONG SU-JI, DAUGHTER
Found something on Seung-ie.
VOTE D-2
Seung-ie, are you asleep?
No, but what's
with the sudden text?
You don't want anyone to find
out about your secret, do you?
WELCOME, PARENTS' DAY
15TH PYRAMID GAME D-1
Attention, everyone.
Moms, dads, if you all wait
in the waiting room,
you'll be able to listen in
on the 5th period class.
I talked Jae-hyeong into it.
She wants to talk
to you guys herself.
Hi, guys.
So, this is where you hang out?
It's nice.
It's got a youthful vibe.
You don't mind if I come up
here sometimes, do you?
Has she always been so bubbly?
-So, you'll cooperate with us?
-Yes!
I like Ja-eun.
Turns out there was real power
behind this frail looking body.
Not because of the photo?
Photo? What photo?
I don't know what that is,
but can I give you a word of
advice now that we're a team?
Don't think this'll be easy.
Especially Ha-rin.
Yu-rim betrayed
you last year, right?
How did you...
Do you know why?
I do.
I just happened to see
how Ha-rin got to her last year.
Ha-rin knows exactly
how to manipulate everyone.
She's the queen bitch.
Ra Hae-jun, Song Jae-hyeong,
Joo Seung-ie, and us three.
The Ds now have an alliance.
There's also one
addition to the plan.
2-5 PARENTS' WAITING ROOM
I didn't see him last year.
Oh...
Oh, Do-ah's mom.
Hello, how have you been?
Are you Seong Su-ji's father?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry to ask,
but how much do you know
about your
daughter's school life?
By any chance, do you like me?
-What?
-You voted for me.
And kept trying to help me.
You're really something.
You're hilarious.
Or do you just loathe her?
Baek Ha-rin.
You told me before
that you play this game
to keep your secret.
I know now.
The secret, your weakness
that Ha-rin is holding over you.
There can only be one thing.
It's Sim Eun-jeong, isn't it?
So, are you trying
to blackmail me?
I just told you
I know what Ha-rin knows.
What do you think I'll do?
You're like her.
-What do you want?
-That was quick.
I want you to become the F
in the next game.
What?
Born rich and a trainee
at a major entertainment agency.
You're pretty and get top grades.
If you become the F,
will the kids be
able to bully you?
-No.
-It'll disrupt the order.
Don't you want
to screw Ha-rin over?
I believe she's independent,
and conducts herself well.
You have no idea
what's happening at school,
but you simply believe
that everything is okay
with your child?
There is bullying
going on in class 2-5.
Why do you think
I'll go along with this?
Because you were the only girl
who opposed to this game.
Right?
This is my plan.
The pyramid?
Fuck it.
PYRAMID GAME