I betrayed my friends.
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
The prisoner's dilemma.
A psychological game where
betrayal makes everyone lose,
but working together
benefits everyone.
When I first came here,
I hated you all.
That's a fault?
I still hate all of you,
most of the time.
I secretly took photos
of you guys.
Mostly of your delts.
I'm sorry.
I'm a pretty good liar.
I...
Ages ago...
You're too nice
and that makes me look bad.
And you,
stop acting like a heroine.
Seong Su-ji,
Be nicer when you talk!
And Ja-eun,
don't be so nice when you talk.
Yeah, you need to be shot.
Ji-ae, why are you
suddenly so quiet?
-You're the one being too loud.
-Are you dissing me?
-You are a bit loud.
-I think she's funny.
You're smiling?
Stop being so nice.
This is funny?
Why are you smiling?
-Stop smiling.
-Stop firing at me.
Hey!
I've racked my brains,
and that's all we've ever done.
What about you?
You know what?
You've been totally
screwed over right now,
and we have finally
become a "we."
Look at her staring.
I feel sorry for her.
Oh no.
Shit, we've been screwed.
Don't just stand there.
Don't you see Ha-rin signaling?
Do you want to see
her flip out again?
Do something.
Pyo Ji-ae.
Come over here.
Shit, come over here!
You think I can't touch you
because you're not an F anymore?
-Stop it.
-What?
-Fuck, get out of my way.
-I said, stop it.
You bitches!
Damn you!
Ja-eun, call 911, now!
Ja-eun, hurry!
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON THE WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
EPISODE 8
Shit!
AUNT
Those girls finally
got into major trouble!
So, how badly is she hurt?
Okay.
Okay, you idiot!
Just wait. Okay?
I'm hanging up!
MR. IM 2-5
I should've been
more attentive.
I don't need an apology.
Our first priority is to stop
them from talking.
The girls, teachers,
and instructors...
-This can't get out.
-Of course.
I'll make sure of that.
When Mr. Kim arrives...
That girl...
Sim Eun-jeong.
She's a scholarship
student, isn't she?
What the hell happened?
Who beat up who?
Go Eun-byeol.
She set me up, didn't she?
She threw me under
the bus, didn't she?
Am I right or not?
You just realized that now?
I'm gonna kill her!
DAD
Don't answer that, damn it!
Where's Baek Ha-rin?
Where is she right now?
Dumbass.
Get your head on straight.
You think that bitch
will help you with your father?
Don't kid yourself.
Acting like her maid
was all for nothing.
Get it together!
Do-ah.
What did she just say to me?
You're just our
driver's daughter.
You think we're friends because
we let you hang out with us?
Know your place.
Don't act like we're friends.
You're nothing but
a servant, Seol-ha.
You do what I tell you!
Got that?
Go get me some alcohol.
Screw you.
Seong Su-ji will win.
What?
At least she knows
who's on her side and who isn't.
Yes, Dad?
BS DAD
Things are bad.
Right now, Eun-jeong...
who is not an F,
got beat up by Da-yeon
who isn't an A.
That's not allowed.
So Ha-rin.
just hear me out.
I'm saying this for your sake.
Why don't you just
do away with the game?
Let's just go with
outright bullying.
Oh. Of course, you would
never bully anyone.
Leave that to us.
To me.
-It has to be the Pyramid Game.
-What?
We're going to play a game today.
If you do well,
you'll get a reward.
But if you don't,
you'll get a penalty.
Having fun?
We're playing a game.
It has to be...
the game.
Got that?
Hey, there's Ja-eun.
Ja-eun, come and play!
Ja-eun! Hurry up!
Ja-eun, come on!
Ja-eun, let's play!
I expected as much.
You don't look guilty at all.
-And you're back from the dead.
-I'm only asking, just in case.
You have no intention
of stopping, or feel any remorse,
do you?
If you do, even just
a little bit, tell me now.
I'll take it under consideration.
Why are you asking me?
-What?
-Go ask Ja-eun.
Hey...
You don't have anything to wear,
right? I'll lend you mine.
Huh?
Geez, put that away.
How is she supposed to fit
into your size zero clothes?
Here, wear mine.
Mine too.
Are you kidding?
You're over 174 cm tall!
Don't you know your own bodies?
Thanks.
Thank you, really.
Come on.
Why is everyone so down?
Yeah!
What's the problem?
Hey, something
The vibe is so chilly
Of course it is.
How is Eun-jeong anyway?
I'm sure she'll call
once the test results are out.
Where's Su-ji?
I think she went out for a sec.
So, including Su-ji,
these are the final members?
Wait a sec.
What are they doing here?
Did Ha-rin tell you to spy on us?
Or are you just here
to check things out?
That's enough.
They were worried
about Eun-jeong.
We'll be choosing an F
among you four.
Who agrees?
Ye-rim. I feel so bad.
I'm sure Eun-jeong
will be alright.
She's got strong bones.
Anyway, you must be
livid with Da-yeon.
Ha-rin and I are on your side.
We think the as should
penalize Da-yeon.
What do you want to do to her?
Tell me anything you want.
Shit, this is what you
wanted to talk about?
This is all I have to say.
Then, I'll take it that
you're leaving everything to us.
Don't change your mind later!
What an attention hog.
HA-RIN
Ha-rin, I did what you asked.
Still no word from Eun-jeong?
Her swim coach just got there,
so I'm sure I'll hear
something soon.
Who's that?
Uh...
Eun-jeong was moved
to Seosim Hospital in Seoul,
and she'll be getting
surgery there.
You saw what happened,
and I know
I don't have to tell you this,
but don't let your imaginations
go into overdrive and exaggerate
what was only an accident.
Make sure word
of this doesn't get out.
A cover up.
It's not something
he could do alone.
Your parents,
the principal...
Most of all,
Eun-jeong's parents
just want to move on quietly.
Do you understand?
Unbelievable.
Fine, extort all
the money you want.
This is why I told you to go
easy on the pranks.
Why are girls' high
schools worse?
Kim Da-yeon.
When we go back to Seoul,
you'll be cleaning the hallway
for two months, got that?
You're not convening a meeting
of the anti-bullying committee?
What?
The anti-bullying committee?
Didn't you girls always
say this was just a game?
Seong Su-ji.
Why are you being so dramatic?
An anti-bullying committee?
That's funny.
COACH
Eun-jeong might have to
give up her swimming career.
You should come and console her.
Clean? Can I make
my housekeeper do it?
What a pain.
Ah...
Why you...
Have you been drinking? Huh?
-You bitch!
-Ye-rim, no.
-Ye-rim!
-You fucking bitch!
-This is all on you!
-Shim Eun-jeong's girlfriend.
Let go of me.
She didn't die, did she?
She's alive,
so what more do you want?
Let go of me!
I only went easy on you
because you're rich.
What, you bitch?
Ye-rim.
Jae-hyeong, hold her back.
This is all your fault!
-Jae-hyeong, grab her.
-Stop it!
Im Ye-rim!
You think I won't give out
penalty points on a school trip?
Aren't you going to debut?
Don't you want a
clean student record?
Ye-rim!
Just shut up.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's start the strip show.
You bitches!
-Ye-rim!
-Don't hold me back!
Let go of me!
Ye-rim, let her go.
I'll make sure she pays.
Shit!
This is a message from the As.
Kim Da-yeon will soon be
receiving a penalty.
What?
What are you doing?
What are you doing, huh?
So, you absolutely refuse
to give up the game?
Fine,
let's go all the way.
Hey, Eun-jeong. I'm here.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Are you okay?
You look comfy.
Have you eaten
anything yet, ma'am?
It's my fault again...
It's my fault...
MISSED CALL
MOM
Ja-eun,
you must be busy.
Are you back in Seoul?
A friend got hurt
because of me.
I'm scared.
I'm miserable, Mom.
STUDY PERIOD
BAEK HA-RIN
GO EUN-BYEOL
CHOI YU-HYUN
YANG SO-YOUNG
IF THERE WAS SOMETHING YOU COULD
DO ANONYMOUSLY, WOULD YOU?
I heard rumors
about class 2-5.
The special class?
What kind of rumors?
Finals are coming up.
Let's study, girls.
You teenagers.
Don't you want to go to college?
You know that girl? The reserve
on the national swim team?
Sim Eun-jeong?
I heard Kim Da-yeon beat
her up and blew her knee out.
SIM EUN-JEONG
THE FUTURE OF THE
KOREAN SWIM TEAM,
TRAINING ON THE NATIONAL
TEAM RESERVES...
Are the adults blocking
all the articles?
That girl's family is a mess.
QB's legal team
provided adequate compensation,
and told them
to keep quiet about it.
There are no problems with
the girls at your school, right?
Do-ah, try to keep Ha-rin
in check for a while.
Dad.
Blocking all the articles
is pretty useless at this point.
What do you mean?
There's a messenger app
that all the kids use these days.
Everyone's talking about how
a reserve on the national
swim team got bullied.
Word got around on social media,
hashtag, KDY.
Kim Da-yeon.
Hold on a sec.
Hello?
Oh, yes.
DO-AH
Yesterday?
Yes.
I have hard evidence.
Tell the Chairman
you want to go abroad.
Evidence of my embezzlement?
You can break the story wide up.
I'm her son.
That game you play?
You're not a child anymore.
How dare you bring the
Baekyeon name into it?
You know what
grandma often says to you?
"You fool."
You fool.
The proof of
your embezzlement
isn't the ticking
time bomb, it's me.
Do you not understand?
Don't mess
with me.
Honey.
I just talked to Director Seo.
What's wrong?
STUDY PERIOD
FINALS ARE HERE!!!
Like we said,
the As have reached a decision
on how to punish
B rank Kim Da-yeon
for assaulting
D rank Sim Eun-jeong
during the school trip.
Starting today
Kim Da-yeon
has no rank.
No rank means...
Kim Da-yeon.
Step out.
Didn't you hear me?
Step out, now!
You're being transferred out.
What the fuck?
They can't do this to me!
Fuck!
Shit!
Nice going.
Keep at it.
Sit, you brat.
Fuck off.
I'm your teacher!
I'm trying to help.
How much can your father pay?
You'll have to transfer out,
but depending on the amount,
I can make you look
like the victim
in all of this at
your new school.
What do you say?
You want to talk to your father?
You little bitch!
Stand up straight!
Woah.
Uh, sir...
You ruin everything.
You know that?
Shit!
-She has to transfer out?
-Kim Da-yeon?
I don't believe it. Wow.
What does it mean?
Did they acknowledge
it was bullying?
CLOSE ACCOUNT
Tap this
and the account blows up.
It'll be untraceable.
Easy, right?
Oh, and the IDs and passwords
you asked me to make.
IDS
PASSWORDS
Thank you.
I'll hand it out to the others.
You're going to have them
spread the rumors here?
-What is this, folklore?
-Well, the finals do cover that.
But those adults only know
how to block articles.
Social media is
out of their scope.
I'm impressed.
Brainy Smurf.
I should go.
Thanks.
That face...
I've seen it before.
Ja-eun, what's going on?
Bring Da-yeon back.
#BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
BULLYING #, #BYGH BULLYING
No, you stay low
and go back to class.
I want Da-yeon back.
Then you should've done
a better job.
You did this to yourself.
Don't take it out on me.
-You're not a child anymore.
-I told you not to mess with me.
I told you not to
mess with my game!
You came.
I told her.
Since she cares
about you so much.
What did you decide to do?
The articles went
out this morning.
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
A PRANK, NOT BULLYING,
BUT DEALT WITH SEVERELY
What do you think your job is?
I'm sorry.
-Ha-rin.
-Yes.
School
is the best place to hone your
skills to set you up for life.
Survival.
Leadership.
The habit of being on top!
My precious baby.
I'm going to give you
everything you want.
That is...
As long as you don't act foolish.
Now, go to class.
It's so good.
By the way, Kim Da-yeon...
I guess being transferred out
counts as justice?
Baek Ha-rin is still left...
Oh...
Three girls helped
out anonymously.
Oh Seong-ah,
Yoon Ye-won, Cho Yu-rim.
But we need more girls
to destroy the game.
Also, wait a little longer
for the recording files.
I'm trying to find a way.
I'll do anything to help too.
By the way, I can't believe
we're finally eating malatang
together as a fam.
I'm so touched.
Since when
did this spicy dish
become a symbol of friendship?
And if it's friendship,
where's Ja-eun?
Where's Ye-rim?
Ye-rim had to go to
the practice studio.
I never imagined
I'd be in the same fam as Ye-rim.
Ja-eun went home
because she wasn't hungry.
Hmph.
Why did she lose her appetite
when even Ye-rim
is staying strong?
Always going overboard.
How adorable.
Going overboard?
No, that face...
It was guilt.
This place is really good.
A LIEUTENANT COLONEL USES
CONNECTIONS
TO HOLD MILITARY EVENT?
MOM
Hello?
So-eun told me everything.
Did you...
Did you really
do that to a friend?
Is it true?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Mom...
Why are your eyes all puffy?
Leave me alone.
What?
Hey, Ha-rin.
Woah, things have been so crazy...
However,
even if I forgot about it,
how could you?
Class rep,
aren't you going to
take the finals or not?
What's going on with you?
Move your desks
into single files, now!
Do Mi-yeong, Song Jae-hyeong.
Move the desks on either
end closer to the windows.
Now.
SIM EUN-JEONG
GOOD LUCK ON YOUR TESTS
Good luck on your tests.
1ST PERIOD MATH 2, 2ND PERIOD
LITERATURE, 3RD PERIOD PE
No cheating.
Any questions?
Question 17
was suddenly added, wasn't it?
Question 17?
Question 5 is three.
Six is one.
-One?
-Yes! Three is two.
-Question three is two?
-Four is one.
Five is one.
Seo Do-ah.
What's the answer to question 17?
One.
Shit...
Keep it up a little
longer, girls.
It's the festival after the tests.
Good luck on your next test.
-One is four.
-Four?
Five is two.
Trigonometrical function?
I know.
It's not sine, cosine.
No?
Yeon-du always
gets good grades, right?
I think she was in the 2nd rank
for mid-terms.
Hey, where's Ja-eun?
Oh, she's not here?
Maybe she went home already?
Leave me alone.
Here you go.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
Looks like you'd
rather have some soju.
Do you have some?
It's 50 million won.
A special price for minors.
What's wrong?
Ja-eun is putting up a wall,
all of a sudden.
Hm...
Forget Su-ji
and work with me.
How about it?
Su-ji is a total psycho.
Her ability to relate
is non-existent.
Do you know this voice?
Park Ji-young.
...friends with you, Ja-eun.
Ja-eun? Don't tell me you
secretly planted...
Don't say that about my friend.
Su-ji is awesome.
I envy her for it
and she's a good friend.
I know all about you, Ji-young.
You're Ha-rin's spy.
Get... Get lost.
You don't sell alcohol to minors
but you plant a recording app
on their phones?
Are you nuts?
I have one of Ha-rin too.
She went to see Ja-eun.
If you listen to it,
that makes us accomplices.
Deal?
Deal.
Wow, shouldn't you say
"I don't have to listen.
I believe in her"
for it to be true friendship?
How can I believe
without listening?
That's so like you.
Oh, before that...
Look at this first.
A LIEUTENANT COLONEL USES
CONNECTIONS TO HOLD
MILITARY EVENT?
Any witnesses?
Crazy bastards. At the
barracks of all places, damn it.
No, don't report
it to the higher-ups!
Keep your mouth shut.
It wasn't assault.
It's still an accident for now.
Ye-won, want some?
Hey, Ja-eun.
Can you get my earphones
by your feet?
Ja-eun, let's go get some snacks.
They still have
some melon buns left.
This is on Su-ji.
Ja-eun, if you ruin my pyramid...
That moron.
I'm going to make
Su-ji the bully.
What I do will be much worse
than what you did to Da-yeon.
What?
Wherever she goes,
whatever she does,
or whoever she meets,
I'll make sure everyone
knows she's a bully
for the rest of her life.
Is that what you want?
Don't.
Don't do this, please.
Then, turn your back on her
and go back to being an F.
Go back to your place.
If you do,
I'll leave the other girls alone.
Please, Ja-eun.
You owe me.
Don't you agree?
I...
I'll go back to being the F.
Ja-eun will be really moody
for a while.
Give her some time.
What? Why?
What's going on?
It's okay with me.
So, what's the next
step of our plan?
The girls have put up
with this insane game
for a year and a half.
They'll have realized
Ha-rin is starting to crack,
and that we've become a team.
Let's use that.
Huh?
You know how I said
I'd destroy the game?
But I can't do it alone.
Will you help, Shin-ye?
Let's become safe, together.
All of us.
Hi, Shin-ye.
Hi.
What about Yeon-du?
She hangs out with Ye-rim.
Won't she come over to us?
It's not sine, cosine.
No?
She's on hold for now.
There's something
bothering me about her.
Oh...
If this fails, I'll become the F.
But I won't fail.
Will you join us?
RA HAE-JUN
I'm in.
Just promise
this won't get back to me.
Ja-eun,
whatever Ha-rin did,
I'm not scared this time.
Let's be friends.
This...
was what I wanted
to hear the most
when I was the F.
Think long and hard, Ja-eun.
We're friends, aren't we?
Hey, where's Ja-eun?
She's a part of
your fam, isn't she?
Something came up at home.
I'm curious.
Why didn't you tell anyone
about this sooner?
I'm not judging you.
But even if it was a game,
you must've realized at
some point this wasn't right.
This is bullying.
Because,
we weren't free
from blame either.
And up until now,
we were left alone.
And we were safe
as long as we weren't the F,
if we're being totally honest.
Yeah. I would've
done the same thing.
On the day of the game,
there will be 13 of us.
I'm reaching out to
a few more girls.
Thirteen?
What happens then?
We'll be the majority, and
we'll give up playing the game.
Give up?
-How?
-They've always stressed the fact
that this game
is played by all of us,
but if that is no
longer the case,
the game becomes invalid.
We have to trust each other
for this strategy to work.
It's not Su-ji's usual way
of winning at all.
That's what
I was gonna say, jinx!
Hey, hang on...
-This feels like...
-You're right.
I would never
have thought of this
if it weren't for
a certain moron.
I'll...
go back to being the F.
SIM EUN-JEONG
Shit!
YE-RIM, YOU WILL BE PERFORMING
WITH YOUR MEMBERS
AT BAEKYEON GIRLS'
HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL!
It's not the same one
as last time, right?
It's a different one.
All you have to do is put it
in place, then turn it on.
Will you be okay?
You heard the recording,
didn't you?
It's not enough
just to end the game.
We have to bring Ha-rin down too.
That's why we need this.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
D-DAY
The last Thursday of every month.
The day of the Pyramid Game.
LOOK FORWARD TO THE SURPRISE
GUEST. BAEKYEON FESTIVAL
Ja-eun!
Huh? Ja-eun!
Hey!
-Don't act like we're friends.
-What's going on?
Why did my heart just race?
A Maltese is pretending
to be a Dobermann.
I love it.
Ja-eun, glare at me again.
Are you...
Did you see that?
She's so cool.
What's gotten into her though?
She's gone back
to being her old self.
Did she bomb her test?
You don't know
her at all, do you?
She never got good grades
in the first place.
Hurry.
22ND BAEKYEON GIRLS'
HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL
CONGRATS ON YOUR DEBUT, YE-RIM
NATIONAL TREASURE
Im Ye-rim!
IM YE-RIM
CONGRATS ON YOUR DEBUT, YE-RIM
PASTRIES AND BUNS
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
So cute.
See you at the pool.
Everything's set.
Let's do this.
-Okay.
-Let's do this.
-Let's go.
We can do this.
PYRAMID GAME
12:59
NOVEMBER 30, THURSDAY
Where's Su-ji and Ye-rim?
You're not even looking for me?
I'm still a part of this class.
Get back inside, now!
Go inside.
Go to your classrooms.
Oh no. What happened?
-Oh no.
Because of you...
PYRAMID GAME