subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
Ha-rin.
Where are you going?
I never laugh, I never weep.
In studious awe
the poets brood before
my monumental pose.
Wow.
So pretty.
She's so fair.
Ha-rin, can I post
this on Facebook?
-It's a private account.
-Yeah.
Yes!
The princess of our class.
My bestie, love you!
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
Go on then.
Baek Ha-rin. The kind,
gentle, angelic looking girl.
Please, please stop, Ha-rin.
How do you like the color?
Are you happy?
Ja-eun.
This must be paradise.
Are you okay?
You're not hurt?
That's enough, Da-yeon.
It's dangerous.
It was you, wasn't it?
The crazy bitch
who created this insane game.
Su-ji?
You want me to take you
to the nurse's office?
No, don't say anything yet.
I'm okay.
Thanks.
Doesn't Ha-rin
always look good in Chanel?
-It's Dior yesterday.
-She looks good in anything.
PYRAMID GAME
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
BASED ON WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
13TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
Myeong Ja-eun, Baek Ha-rin.
Who'll be easier?
If only she had
agreed to my plan.
13TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
What if I bring
the ringleader down?
This is Hermès.
It's a calfskin loafer
with an elegant fringe,
and the signature "H" detail.
The "H" buckle is
in rose gold
on a feminine fringe detail.
These shoes are
classic and elegant
with a slim design.
Stop.
I'll do whatever you want.
Just stop it, please.
Do whatever you want with me.
Just don't bully the others.
Ha-rin.
The others?
Who?
You mean...
Seong Su-ji?
Ja-eun.
You're actually
worried about Su-ji?
Liar.
That's not who you are.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NAME: SEONG SU-JI
NOTES: RAISED BY SINGLE FATHER
FATHER - CAREER SOLDER,
LIEUTENANT COLONEL
WRITING CONTEST 1ST PRIZE, ESSAY
2ND PRIZE HONORS IN ALL SUBJECTS
LOW DEPENDENCY, INDIVIDUALISTIC
-Mr. Im!
-Yes?
The meeting.
Oh, right.
During the juniors' mid-terms,
please let's try
to get through it
without any complaints
from the parents.
Okay?
-Got that?
-Yes, ma'am.
I'm counting on you.
Anything else we need to discuss?
-Anything?
-Well...
I think someone is being
bullied in my class.
It's my first time as a homeroom
teacher so I'm not sure...
Based on the
anti-bullying manual...
Oh dear. Are the parents
of that student powerful people?
Excuse me?
Oh, the victim?
No, she's from an ordinary...
What do you mean, "victim"?
You know how
celebrities and athletes
have their careers ruined
with even the mention
of having been
bullies in the past.
I always felt bad about that.
As an educator,
if you actually look into it,
most were just
harmless pranks as a teenager.
These kids have
a whole future ahead.
Do you really want
to bring them down?
Besides, determining
what's bullying
and what's not can be
so ambiguous.
If you say things
like that in public,
you could end up in
a lot of trouble, ma'am.
You never know
what teenage kids will do
if you try to
take care of things too hastily.
You should talk to the student
being bullied first.
I'm telling you,
they're just kidding around.
I just need to hang in there.
Just a little longer.
Already?
Gu Seol-ha, let her go.
Dang it.
We were just getting started.
Oh dear.
Her legs gave out.
Break is over.
Go back to your seats.
Okay.
I've learned a few things.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Settle down.
Are you ready to start class?
Recess is ten minutes.
Things are much easier to handle
if I can avoid them for
ten minutes. Funny isn't it?
Ten minutes during break,
60 minutes during lunch.
They only harass
me during that time.
They don't touch
me after school,
and make sure
never to leave a trace.
They can only go after Fs
if they're a level A
or have an A's permission.
The fact that
there are these blind spots
means that there
are rules to the game
and everyone follows them.
Were these rules made by
Baek Ha-rin as well?
It feels like everything
is set up for this game.
Even the fact that our class
is in a different building
from the others.
If this isn't a coincidence,
this isn't just the act
of Baek Ha-rin,
who's only a student.
"Nature blows your mind."
Nature blows your mind.
This means...
That it captivates your mind.
It engages you...
A conscience response
or a reflex.
Differentiating the two
depends on where
the order comes from.
If your cerebrum
sends a signal, and you react...
That's a conscience response.
Do the teachers really not know?
When everything is so obvious?
Security cameras?
Being an ENTP-type
I'm naturally curious.
There are cameras
in the main building
but why don't we have any?
Your class is the only one there.
What's the point of
having cameras there?
Don't you think? Oh!
You have a human
security camera too. Do-ah.
That girl is so dependable.
Her family runs Seosim Hospital
so no wonder she's so different.
I wish I had her in my class.
I'm so jealous.
Seosim Hospital?
NAME: SEO DO-AH - FATHER:
DIRECTOR OF SEOSIM HOSPITAL
Don't even try to ask Mr.
Im for help.
-Hello.
Hi.
SEOSHIM HOSPITAL SEO DO-AH
QB GROUP CONCLUDES AGREEMENT
WITH SEOSIM HOSPITAL
BAEK HA-RIN
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL,
GU SEOL-HA WINS BRONZE
IN NATIONAL JUDO COMPETITION
THREE TO REPRESENT
SEOUL IN GIRLS' JUDO
AT NATIONAL JUNIOR
SPORTS COMPETITION
Judo? No wonder...
GU SEOL-HA
QB GROUP SPONSORS
BRONZE MEDALIST GU SEOL-HA
SIM EUN-JEONG
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
TOP TALENT ALL IN ONE SCHOOL
A SURPRISING NETWORK
OF GOLDEN CONNECTIONS
SIM EUN-JEONG, IM YE-RIM,
YOON YE-WON, JEONG YEON-DU
Wow, this is no joke.
How can they all be in
the same class?
What is with this class?
In today's society,
both the rich and the poor
carry Chanel bags and drive BMWs.
The class difference nowadays
comes from people's manners.
The virtues you need to inhabit
should be respect,
politeness, honesty,
responsibility, and care.
The proof of one's high
class will show when people
have small talk or how they treat
service workers in restaurant
or when they make small purchases
with black cards.
You better come home early today.
If you're not here,
who's going to be on
the receiving end of
Dad's baseball bat?
People, be kind.
Seung-ie, can you come with me
to buy a used item today?
I found the stickers I wanted!
Can't you just buy a new one?
Fine.
-Yes! You'll come with me?
-Sure.
Seung-ie.
Come over here a sec.
You want some vitamins?
I'm good.
Did you know?
That Kim Da-yeon was the
youngest daughter of QB Group?
Oh, you didn't?
There are a lot of special
kids in our class.
Oh...
Do you mind if
I ask you something?
Since I have no
one else to talk to.
Sure.
What is it?
Who do you think made this game?
I mean, why do you think they
made a crazy game like this?
Oh, am I the only one curious?
Just hypothetically,
if it had been you,
why would you have made it?
For fun.
Fun.
When you see the others
watching you get bullied,
don't you just want to
dig their eyes out?
They'll never know
the look in their eyes
when they look at the F.
I'd want to dig their eyes out
and show them.
Oh, but then, I guess they
wouldn't be able to see at all.
That means, they'll never know.
Isn't that funny?
If that's what they're thinking,
that would be so scary.
Right?
Yeah...
Sounds like a psychopath.
Just got the chills.
I've been thinking...
Why me though?
They already have
Myeong Ja-eun, so why?
Just to stomp out
any potential defiance
because I'm new?
Who knows?
But Su-ji,
it's not your fault.
Baek Ha-rin...
You're more bizarre
than I imagined.
Can I honestly say
going after her
would be easier
than persuading Ja-eun?
Absolutely not.
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Why do you keep disappearing
during every recess?
Do you have any idea
what it does to the rest of us?
Because of you and
Ja-eun, Seung-ie...!
If we get bullied instead of you,
it'll be on you!
Are you out of your mind?
What?
Why is that on me?
You guys hate being
bullied so much
but you expect me to just take it
while they beat
me and torture me?
Why should I let them
just so you guys can be safe?
Because you're an F!
You're a lower rank than us!
If you think that sucks,
try to up your level!
Pyo Ji-ae!
Ah, I should just
keep my head down.
Girls like Go Eun-byeol
could get scared
and back down if I keep this up.
I don't have time to deal with
wimps like this.
I need at least two votes
until the next vote.
The best scenario right now is
for Eun-byeol, Ja-eun
and me to trade votes.
That'll put us above Pyo Ji-ae
and Joo Seung-ie who are Ds.
Hey, we're not done here!
Myeong Ja-eun
is the only way.
I don't know what I did wrong.
School feels like hell,
and I can't bring
myself to tell my dad.
Su... Su-ji...
I'm sorry.
What I said to you about filing
a report or transferring...
I guess I spoke too easily
since it wasn't happening to me.
And my plan
to bring someone else down...
That was so mean.
I was just so desperate.
Can you just do me one favor?
You and I should
vote for each other.
That's okay, isn't it?
Fall for it, naive and
innocent Myeong Ja-eun.
I can't.
Uh, I mean...
I just don't play that game.
What? Why not?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
What?
A burn bandage?
Were you...
This is a cigarette burn,
isn't it?
-Did Baek Ha-rin do this?
-No. No.
Yeah, right.
You always smelled of cigarettes
and I thought it was strange.
You sure have an unlimited
amount of tolerance, don't you?
By any chance, you're not
a masochist, are you?
Ja-eun, are you okay with the
way things are? Are you happy?
I know you're in so much pain,
that you do this to yourself.
I know you want this to stop.
Am I wrong?
Whatever, I can't do it.
What don't you try asking
Seung-ie and Ji-ae?
I'll ask them for you,
if you want.
What?
Who would ask who?
Seung-ie and Ji-ae are both nice.
They even talk to me sometimes.
And Seung-ie is nice about
lending you stuff.
She doesn't swear either.
When the others
ask her for favors,
she does them
without ever getting mad.
So, if you ask her...
Oh, I see.
She must be really nice.
But do you know
the difference between being
nice and being a doormat?
You want me to show you?
What?
Piss off!
I don't owe you a vote.
You should be apologizing to us
for getting
bullied instead of you.
-How shameless can you be?
-Forget it, Seung-ie.
-Don't bother talking to her.
-You're nuts. I'm no doormat!
You're an F. Do you think
we're on the same level?
You're crazy.
-Let's go.
-Geez!
See?
And you thought they were nice?
Because they didn't
bully you outright?
Those girls... Actually,
the entire class probably
wants you to be the F.
As long as possible.
That's the only way they survive.
That's how humans are.
It's the smart thing to do.
And you. You're not the nice
girl. You're just a doormat.
Get your head
on straight, Ja-eun.
From this point on,
just focus on getting
out of being the F with me...
What the...?
Did her feelings get hurt?
I should go.
Hey!
All the girls were in
the same class last year as well.
They were all in class 1-5
in their sophomore year.
Only Ja-eun and me were
new to the class.
Class 1-5?
So that's why it was
the 13th game.
That means it started
around June last year.
By the way, Su-ji...
You didn't tell Ja-eun
about me, did you?
Eun-byeol is just the same
as the others.
She pretends to care
about Ja-eun,
but won't do anything to help.
I don't have an ulterior motive.
I just don't want
Ja-eun to be upset.
I'm no different.
If I tell Ja-eun about Eun-byeol
and the two make up,
I could be left out in the cold.
Like I said,
this is how humans are.
Humans are all
selfish and self-centered,
Ja-eun.
DAD
TRAINING AN ELITE REGIMENT
THAT WINS IN BATTLE / UNIT 6694
Oh, hey.
-Here.
-Thanks.
See you at home.
About changing schools...
Oh, did the date move up?
When are we leaving?
You don't have to change
schools anymore.
-What?
-My work got extended.
You'll be able to graduate
at this school.
You'll be a senior next year
so this is good.
See you.
No, Dad.
I'm totally fucked.
Seo Do-ah.
Myeong Ja-eun.
Ja-eun is absent again today?
Sheesh.
Okay, open your books...
I made a mistake that day.
You're not the nice girl.
You're just a doormat.
Get your head
on straight, Ja-eun.
Just focus on getting out
of being the F with me...
I should go.
I shouldn't have
thrown it in her face like that.
X goes over here.
X-1/X2 minus 3X+2.
Now that?
When the X goes here
what happens to the denominator?
It goes over to 0.
Do you feel sorry for her?
-Should we help her out?
-No.
Convergence, 0/0.
How do you do this?
Let's factorize the
number on top first.
The first one.
What happens now?
Limit X...
Get your head
on straight, Ja-eun.
Just focus on getting out
of being the F with me...
I should go.
Hey!
Why didn't you come to school?
You'll be here tomorrow, right?
I went too far yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Did you become
friends with Su-ji?
Don't tell me
school became fun for you.
I think that would
make me sick.
What should I do?
WHY DIDN'T YOU COME TO SCHOOL?
I WENT TOO FAR YESTERDAY.
COME TO SCHOOL, JA-EUN
There will be a special
performance by the ballet club.
Su-ji.
Su-ji, go fetch.
A rifle?
My dad's hobby is hunting.
I borrowed it,
thinking I needed it for you.
Su-ji. Seong Su-ji.
Did you think you
could just avoid us?
For how long?
Guess what happens
when hunting dogs
outlive their use?
They die.
As if she's going shoot me.
The hell she will.
You guys never leave
evidence behind.
And Baek Ha-rin will have a fit.
Da-yeon, you look so awesome.
I'm dying here.
Don't worry.
There won't be any evidence.
This only fires tranquilizers.
Go get the bunny.
Looking for someone?
You don't look too good.
You want some of this at least?
It's only black tea for my diet.
Do you know who's
behind this game?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Were you looking for Baek Ha-rin?
I thought...
It's obvious?
You mean, everyone knows?
Mom.
I'm sure they do.
As well as the fact that
she's the Director's daughter.
The Director?
Director Choi Ie-hwa
of Baekyeon Group,
one of Korea's top three
conglomerates,
received commendation today
for the contributions made
to the advancement of education.
Baekyeon Group...
She's the granddaughter.
This way, please.
The steak
is nice and tender.
Director Seo, let me ask
you something.
How can you explain this,
medically?
Look. Baekyeon Group
only has one daughter.
Seosim Hospital
And us, QB...
Daughters only too.
Are you sure this
is a coincidence?
Can this really be a coincidence?
Everyone's X chromosome
was just dominant.
By the way, Ha-rin, which
university are you applying to?
If it's okay with you,
how about working
on your portfolio with Do-ah?
I think it'll bring
you two closer,
and working together
will make you stronger.
We're already close.
Do-ah is smart and cute.
Cute?
Thanks.
Are you still hanging out
with that judo athlete?
I'm closer to Ha-rin.
Oh, Dad.
Could you support the school's
swim team with more scholarships?
A girl named Eun-jeong in our
class has talent but she's poor.
Please don't say no.
Please? Please?
All right, let's do that.
Why don't we have a drink?
All right.
13TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
I have to throw it out anyway.
It's ten minutes
past the expiration date.
It won't kill you.
DROP-OUT FORM
PRINT
VIOLENCE ISN'T A JOKE.
IT'S A CRIME
NO MORE SCHOOL VIOLENCE
CALL 117
The game? Our homeroom
teacher probably doesn't know.
If he did, he might want to help.
He knows a lot about
the class dynamics
and everyone's
personal information.
He even cares about kids
like Ja-eun too.
Our homeroom teacher...
How many bullying incidents
are solved by teachers?
Maybe one out of ten?
Mr. Im isn't the type that's
close with the students either.
Seong Su-ji.
Nothing's going on, is it?
Ja-eun keeps missing school...
Just let me know
if something's up in class.
You can come to me about
personal issues too.
He does seem to care...
Whether it works or not,
it's worth a try.
I need another plan anyway.
Uh, Mr. Im...
Mr. Im.
The principal is looking for you.
You're going over to
Myeong Ja-eun's house? Right now?
Yes.
She's been skipping school a lot.
You work pretty hard.
Would he be able to convene an
anti-bullying committee meeting?
Even if the person behind it is
the school director's daughter?
Seong Su-ji.
I guarantee
your situation will only get
worse if you try to fight it.
Based on what?
Only one person in this class
has ever tried
to stop this game.
Today, we're going to
learn about Spinoza...
Someone in this class
was against this game?
So what?
They've all given up
and going along with it now.
That's your reason, Do-ah?
This means,
that the girl who forced her
to stand down is Ha-rin.
One week before the next game.
Will I be able to get
out of being an F?
You still have a low fever.
But I can't let you stay here
for two periods in a row.
Go back to class for now,
and if you keep feeling
unwell, you should go home.
Go back to class?
Rest a little
and leave when you're ready.
Your situation will only
get worse if you try to fight it.
Will only get worse.
-Hello.
Hi.
I don't know what it is
with kids these days.
I tried to break up
what looked like a fight
but they said they were playing.
Is that what they call
"play" these days?
Haha, hoho.
They're really different
from our day.
They're so tough and intense.
I just don't get it.
How can that be joking around?
Wow, big ass.
You think that's playing?
Of course it isn't.
Is your next class PE?
What's so funny?
Are you sure you're
all getting along?
Mr. Im, no nagging on our break.
This is how we always play.
Right, Su-ji?
Oh, Mr. Im.
What's wrong?
Oh, well...
Mr. Im, can you take me
to the nurse's office?
I think I'm coming
down with a cold.
-I'll go with her.
-No, I'll go with Mr. Im.
Yes, you have class.
Is it okay if I take her?
-Sure.
-Let's go, Su-ji.
You wanted to talk?
Can an anti-bullying
committee meeting
be held for our class too?
I've been concerned
about you as it is.
Why?
Are the kids bullying you?
Yes.
Can you help?
There was a student named Wu-ri
in that class last year.
She was bullied, like you.
Ja-eun is going through
the same thing, isn't she?
I might
be able to help you.
Thank God.
Thank you.
I appreciate you telling me.
Su-ji.
Can you tell me again
what happened looking
into the camera?
Are you ready?
Did you see Seong Su-ji?
She's doomed.
Watch out for Mr. Im.
She must not know
that he's psycho.
-Poor girl.
-I feel sorry for her.
How did she end up as his prey?
She's dumber than I thought.
As if he wouldn't know
what's going on.
I know. He's money crazy.
Money crazy?
Totally.
What if Su-ji ends up
like Cho Wu-ri?
No way.
Do you have any bruises
or scrapes?
Huh? No?
Having a cigarette burn
would be effective too.
In matters like, we need evidence.
But kids these days
are so clever,
they don't leave a mark.
They're still wet
behind their ears
but they've learned
all the tricks.
Hmph.
Damn it.
Damn...
Come on,
you need a burn mark.
Su-ji, if we can get evidence,
I'll tell their parents.
We can split the
compensation money.
Huh? Look at me.
Clench your jaw. Here we go.
Seong Su-ji! Are you in there?
Seong Su-ji!
Damn, what the hell?
Are you in there?
Su-ji, are you in there?
Hey!
Ow...
Su-ji, pull it together.
Let's go!
Seong Su-ji. Myeong Ja-eun.
Hello, Mr. Im.
That way.
Hello.
-Hello.
Are you mental?
Don't you know
what kind of person he is?
What were you doing with him?
He could've really hurt you.
Mr. Im... I mean...
Is he insane?
I'm sorry, I should've told you.
I...
The camera is rolling.
Here comes the strip show.
What? A strip show?
Who was this?
It was a penalty.
Mr. Im would've told
Da-yeon's parents
about the bullying
and blackmailed them
saying you're the proof.
For money.
Then Da-yeon would've
gotten back at you.
This is what would've happened.
That's Wu-ri.
Cho Wu-ri.
You agreed
to play the game, right?
PYRAMID GAME
SEONG SU-JI
THE HIGHEST FORM OF PENALTY
WILL BE APPLIED
IF THE GAME IS DISCLOSED
I AGREE TO THE RULES
That's the penalty?
They're all insane.
Did he hit you too?
No.
I don't play the game.
Are you okay?
Wait, he hit you?
Don't worry about it.
These tears are just a reaction.
I'm sorry, Su-ji.
This is my fault.
It's my fault.
But it'll be over soon.
What?
How did you know
where to find me though?
Oh...
DROP-OUT FORM
GUIDANCE COUNSELOR'S OFFICE
Uh...
-Ha-rin.
-Please tell Mr. Im
to just shut up and teach
as if he's barely there.
Do you understand?
Yes.
He's done
this before but he wasn't fired?
I know this is a private school,
but that means
he has connections.
Someone related to Baek Ha-rin.
We should've held on to his phone.
It's proof.
Huh?
Oh, I didn't think about that.
Oh, well.
But thanks. I can start
thinking straight again.
By the way, were you
ever friends with Go Eun-byeol?
No.
She told me the two of you joined
the class when
you became juniors.
I did. Me and...
It wasn't Eun-byeol.
What was that nutjob
trying to do then?
Ja-eun,
I have a favor to ask.
Please, play the game.
I really want to escape
from being an F with you.
I mean it.
I'm sorry.
It'll be over soon.
Once I drop out.
-You're dropping out?
-Yes.
If I'm not here,
the situation for you
will change too.
This game
will never end,
just because you're gone.
This has been going on
because Baek Ha-rin isn't alone.
The rest are all the same.
Being a monster rubs off.
You saw for yourself.
You're crazy. Piss off!
I'm no doormat!
We need evidence...
Someone has to stop it
for this to truly end.
This class has to change.
No, let me rephrase that.
Let's destroy the Pyramid Game.
That's the only answer.
Right?
Hey.
Don't you know how
to greet a teacher?
-Hello.
-Good.
But you're not a teacher.
You're parasite in this class.
That's how kids talk these days.
What?
Why you...
Damn...
Hello.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Good morning.
I'm going to call roll. Sit down.
Seong Su-ji, hurry up and sit.
Who's late? Myeong Ja-eun?
She's always late.
You know what tomorrow is, right?
The last Thursday of the month.
Be there.
Blue wind,
mark it with a star.
Blue is sight.
Wind is touch.
What does it mean?
Your senses...
That's all for today.
Thank you.
Ji-ae.
Can you stop being so noisy
when you eat?
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
ONE HOUR BEFORE
THE PYRAMID GAME
Ja-eun, you're
really not coming...
Ah...
Who are you voting for today?
If you don't have anyone
to vote for, vote for me.
I want to be an A too.
Yeah, vote for one of us.
-Let's just go.
-Hmph.
SEPTEMBER 28, THURSDAY
Let's start H.R.
Take your seats.
-You're going to play?
-Yes.
Then sit.
I thought you were ghosting me.
I had a lot to think about.
You're right.
This game can't go on.
Did you get the text?
The link for the app.
You know the rules
so I'll skip the explanation.
Then cast your votes
for the 14th Pyramid Game.
OPEN LINK
DOWNLOADING PYRAMID GAME APP
PYRAMID GAME
Listen carefully.
According to the rules,
the F has to have zero votes.
If you and I vote for each other
you, me, Pyo Ji-ae, Joo Seung-ie
will all have one vote.
That makes us all Ds.
We'll be ranked last
but at least we won't be Fs.
That's the loophole in this game.
None of us will be Fs.
This game isn't perfect.
That's where we start.
1 MYEONG JA-EUN
1 SEONG SU-JI
VOTING COMPLETE
14TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
COUNTING VOTES
SEONG SU-JI 5 VOTES
What on earth?
PYRAMID GAME