The reason I trembled
in front of Ha-rin that day...
This was why.
Because of fear.
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL 2-5
DELETE
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON THE WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
EPISODE 7
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
Get up!
Get up, now!
Let's go.
Let's go, guys.
Come on.
Look, a shark.
SEONG SU-JI
Hey, do you know
Ja-eun's Instagram ID?
Eun-byeol.
You're gonna hang
out with Ha-rin
during free time
Ha-rin later, right?
Can I come with?
So pretty.
How are you going to
destroy the game? Any spoilers?
Can you tell me
who else contacted you?
You're going to take
full blame if this fails, right?
The other girls?
How many have
reached out so far?
At least they're
feeling things out.
Public opinion is wavering.
We can do this!
Hey, they reached
out to me too.
-Seong-ah, Sin-ae, and...
-Let me see.
What? Ji-young? Cut her off!
She's a spy, 100%.
Her parents work at
Baekyeon Food.
What happened
with the recordings though?
You said you were going to
release them this weekend.
Oh, yeah.
What happened?
It's not supposed to be such an
ordinary day enjoying the sun.
I was thinking
we should push it...
Let's go.
Huh?
-Help me up.
-Sure.
Can you anticipate
how far I'll go?
DETAILS OF CORRUPT
LIEUTENANT COLONEL
A hair.
How does it feel
betraying your friends?
Are you disappointed in yourself?
Do you regret
not transferring out?
It's not too late.
-Run when you still can.
-Why?
Why are you doing this?
What is it that you want?
What do I want?
A rift.
Betrayal.
You guys shattering
into little pieces.
Ta-da!
-Got us some tiramisu!
-Thanks.
Here.
DAD
Hello?
How's your trip?
Busan, is it?
Yes.
Okay.
Have a good time
during your three days there.
See you.
Dad.
What?
Never mind.
Congrats, Ye-rim.
You're in the debuting team.
MESSAGE
Hey.
Can you take a photo for us?
Oh, uh... Okay.
She said okay. Go, go, go.
On three, one two, three.
How should we pose next?
-The flower cup pose.
-Flower cup.
Are you all smiling?
What next?
-A heart.
-Okay.
I just got a text
from your coach
asking me to talk to you.
You're not competing
in the next meet?
Are you crazy?
Have you gone completely nuts?
-Don't get so worked up, Ye-rim.
-You stay out of this.
It's because of me.
She agreed to be
my surfing buddy that day.
-What?
-Since I can't swim.
Can you give us some privacy?
It's okay.
Ye-rim will get to debut.
Hey. Don't go!
Eun-jeong!
You want Eun-jeong back?
It all depends on you.
Ye-rim.
I'm pretty sure
I took those in private.
How did you get these?
I know what I did was wrong.
And I won't do it again.
Anyway,
I'm not buying.
Your brother has an interview
at a law firm, doesn't he?
He'll be interviewed by Baekyeon
Group's former corporate lawyer.
I wonder what he'll do if he sees
these photos you've
been collecting?
Will the result of his interview
change or not?
After you're done
with your team activities,
meet back here
at the lobby, got it?
Is that actually fun?
It's more fun than you think.
And it isn't scary at all.
-It's not?
-Yep.
I should've signed up for it too.
What am I gonna do
about my hair?
Who's that?
-Isn't that Ha-rin?
-It's Ha-rin.
Really?
Ha-rin!
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I just slipped.
Da-yeon,
take your cardigan off.
Take it off, now.
Come on!
Can you get up?
The chlorine
is going to ruin your silky hair.
Are you cold?
Baek Ha-rin!
You fell in the pool?
Huh?
I'm so sorry.
And thank you.
I'll keep an eye on the girls.
Thank you.
Fighting in class wasn't enough?
Was this another "prank"?
Are you sure?
Ha-rin, are you okay?
Should I take you to a doctor?
You're all...
Will you shut up?
Shut up, sir.
Right, guess you don't need
a doctor for something so minor.
Do you want to go change?
I've never seen
her this crazy before.
Why did you do it?
What were you going
to do after pushing her in?
What?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
I saw you.
Don't do anything stupid.
Especially, something
you can't handle.
What?
What did I do?
Is this about Ha-rin?
Didn't you hear her?
She said she slipped.
I didn't mean to.
It was a mistake.
Really...
But...
Fuck, don't act so innocent.
I saw everything too.
Are you guys any different?
Ha-rin!
Let's drink up.
-Okay.
Actually,
I think that the game
the kids are playing
is getting a little out of hand.
Don't you think we
should discuss it?
It's just a game.
What's the big deal?
There's a Colonel I run into
sometimes while golfing
and a while ago, he was bragging
that the Chairman
of Baekyeon Group
extended a gesture of goodwill.
The father of the new girl
who came in the summer
is part of that unit.
The game seems to have gone
beyond the classroom,
and I think they
should be cautioned.
Hurry up
and find your own bags.
Thanks.
Check your bags.
Watch your head.
If you have your bags,
move inside.
-Move inside.
-Okay.
Move, move.
-Slowly.
-Move it.
Ha-rin, only our class
is staying at this hotel?
Where's our room? Is it a suite?
If you have your bags,
move inside.
-Come on, let's go.
-If you have...
Move inside.
Is it so hard
assigning your own rooms?
What's taking so long?
Five times five, 25.
Five in each house.
If you don't want me to assign
your rooms for you,
divide into groups, now.
Quickly.
Hae-jun, you want to room with us?
-We don't have five yet.
-Oh, okay. Come on.
Seong-ah, over here.
Okay.
-Shin-ye, wanna come?
-Huh?
Yes.
Do-ah, Da-yeon.
Eun-jeong, come on.
We're done.
Yeah?
Then why are there
three of you left?
Come on.
You three groups,
take one each.
Come on, let's unpack
and get dinner.
It's just one bomb after another.
Ah...
Ji-ae, over here.
Will you be okay?
Cho Yu-rim,
run, run, run.
Wow, I get to room with Ye-rim.
This is great.
I brought a lot
of facial masks too.
You want one later?
Were you and I friends?
So shameless.
The accommodations
are on your right.
Let's go. Move it.
What is that smell?
I smell a traitor.
Were you always like this?
You're not what I expected.
Yeah, and you're
the traitor who made Ja-eun an F.
She snitched on me?
Figures.
She only acts like
she wants to protect other girls.
I'm a victim in this too, you know.
You think I wanted to cut her off?
You think you wouldn't
betray anyone
if you were in the same situation?
All the girls in this class would
do exactly the same thing.
Ja-eun is no different.
Betrayal...
It's a wish. We can write
what we're craving to eat, right?
-That thing I mentioned...
-So, what are we doing?
We writing wishes to send
them up in lanterns later.
-Yeah.
-Oh.
What should we write, Ja-eun?
I'm gonna write
Ja-eun heart Jae-hyeong.
Calm down, Jae-hyeong.
Sheesh.
Here, the instructions.
Wow, there's ours.
So nice.
-It's pretty.
-Yeah.
-Right?
She's sharp.
What'll happen?
Do what I say
when I tell you to.
I'll be in touch.
BAEK HA-RIN / DO WHAT I SAY WHEN
I TELL YOU TO. I'LL BE IN TOUCH
Ha-rin, you're working too hard.
I'll be your lady-in-waiting.
You be the princess of our class.
Those morons might
get the wrong idea.
They might think you're nervous.
It's all my fault.
I had too much free time today.
Right?
You're such a child.
I'll be your lady-in-waiting
all you want
as long as
I get into Hanguk University...
You want the next test papers?
I would appreciate that.
Just do what I tell you tomorrow.
And do it right this time.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
Should I go get
confirmation later?
Ja-eun.
How can you be so nice?
Yu-rim.
She's going to think
you've forgiven her.
I just...
I think we could've been friends
if it weren't for this game.
It just crossed my mind.
It's the same
with the other girls.
How did we end up like this?
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Su-ji
Happy b-day, Su-ji!
-Make a wish!
YE-RIM, I'M IN BUSAN TOO
THIS MUST BE FATE
HAVING FUN?
WITHOUT ME?
POST
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
HAVING A GOOD TIME
MY MESSAGES
If I had noticed
your red flags,
maybe you could've
been friends too.
IF I HAD NOTICED
YOUR RED FLAGS,
MAYBE YOU COULD'VE
BEEN FRIENDS TOO
Friends?
Okay, we're rolling.
Time for the strip show.
Damn it, don't make us wait.
Time is ticking.
CHO WU-RI
You're so fucking slow.
You did nothing wrong.
I'll get you out of that room.
DELETE
Wu-ri's face when she walked
back home all alone at night...
Is this what she looked like?
Yes.
Fucking terrified.
Did I thank you
for that day during dodgeball?
Want it?
Ah...
I really hate making excuses,
but since the app is my baby,
I feel like I'll be forever
labeled as one the bullies too.
If I'm being honest,
I was complicit.
And also,
I wasn't the only one trying
to stay on Ha-rin's good side.
Anyway, just let me know
if there's anything I can do.
I'll help this time.
I swear on my baby.
Why?
Because the ball that hit me
fucking hurt.
What do you want to do?
-Should we just go to bed?
-Let's go to bed.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey, hey.
Already?
-Then, a movie?
-Horror?
And fried chicken?
Are you insane?
Fried chicken at night
is just evil, guys.
Salad?
-I'm going to bed.
-Come on.
Okay, then chicken salad.
Oh, shit!
Ja-eun, you go.
I almost had a heart attack.
Go see who it is.
Who-who-who is it?
-What is all that?
-Huh?
Spicy fried chicken.
I can't resist half-and-half
of original and spicy.
Today's my cheat day.
Bring it over!
Let's dig in!
Are we...
making you uncomfortable?
-No, why?
-Just asking.
You don't look so happy.
Yeah, Su-ji.
Are you not feeling well?
You've been down all day.
DELETE
I...
I've been wanting to talk to you.
When you said you were
going to get rid of the game,
you looked...
so cool.
I'm sorry, Su-ji.
For ignoring you before.
Want some cake?
We have some of
Su-ji's birthday cake left.
Yeah, sounds good.
I'll go get it.
Happy b-day.
You did nothing wrong.
Su-ji, hurry up!
-Do you need a bag?
-No, I'm good.
That'll be 2,500 won.
Hey guys, focus.
Has anyone seen Ha-rin?
-She's not in her room?
-No, that's why I'm asking.
Crap.
I've always wanted to treat you
the way you treated the girls.
Fuck.
Da-yeon.
-Hey, I'm an A.
-So?
You'll be nothing
once we graduate.
Maybe you'll go to college,
get a job, and join the
rat race, but that's it.
-What about Ha-rin?
-What?
You just don't get it, do you?
The Pyramid Game will continue
even if we graduate.
Like an extended version.
Don't you see?
The Pyramid Game is Ha-rin.
Maybe she went out for a walk.
I need to discuss
tomorrow's big event.
Why...
Why aren't you
doing anything to me?
You turned around.
You saw me.
Someone other than you
pissed me off even more.
Don't worry.
You won't become an F.
You're nothing.
I'm gonna look terrible tomorrow.
-You're gonna be all puffy.
-You too.
Your face is puffy already.
Someone's phone is buzzing.
Here, Ja-eun.
Your phone.
Thanks.
Hello?
Mom.
-Ja-eun!
-Mom.
How have you been?
So-eun said I should come
see you since you're in Busan.
You're in the same
school and class?
Why didn't you tell me?
You used to be best friends.
Here, strawberries.
Share them with your friends.
They're sweeter than last year.
I wish I could give some to your
homeroom teacher,
but I don't want you girls
to get scolded because I came.
I'll get going.
You girls go in too.
I hope we get to see
each other more often.
With Ja-eun too.
It's a boarding school where
Pastor Hwang is a board member.
It's one of the best boarding
schools in the States.
Why do you want
to send Ha-rin away?
She should've gone sooner.
She doesn't need
a Korean education,
and I should've set her on the
path to an Ivy League school.
Pastor Hwang recommends it too.
-She can still...
-You're dismissed.
Mother.
This is the best you
could come up with?
Can't you be more
ambitious like Ha-rin?
You fool...
There's no knowing what she'll do.
Friends?
You heard her.
Your best friend
is So-eun.
That's why you jumped in.
Unlike the other girls.
Without any hesitation.
Ha-rin!
Your friendship
made me want to
kill you even more.
So-eun.
You hypocrite.
Stop.
Just stop.
Stop this.
If you don't care about your
mom finding out your secret,
then should we talk
about your mom?
-What...
-Oh.
By the way, Su-ji betrayed
you to protect her dad.
What will you do?
MYEONG JA-EUN
What? Who's there?
Su-ji? Why are you
wandering around
like a ghost in the
middle of the night?
Go back to bed.
You're out too?
Why you...
Where have you been?
Go back inside, now.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Things have been
a wreck in our class lately.
I know it must've
been tough on you.
Since there are no Fs,
the balance has been thrown off.
Today's game is a team game,
but it also includes
an individual game.
If you're shot more than three
times, there will be a penalty.
It'll be a little extreme since
you'll be taking the F's place.
Ja-eun.
-Last night, by any chance...
-It's okay.
We're supposed to
move on our own, right?
I'll go this way.
See you later.
Be careful.
This is fun.
You're out if you get shot
three times, right?
What?
You can miss a swim meet for me,
but you can't take the penalty?
It'll be a little extreme
since you'll be taking
the F's place.
Wu-ri dropped out of school?
She got a penalty for trying
to tell the teacher.
How bad was it for
her to drop out?
I don't know for sure,
but I heard it was a strip show.
Aren't you curious
what the penalty will be?
You bitch! If you hadn't
come to our school,
if it weren't for you...!
This is all your fault!
You and that outcast
Myeong Ja-eun! Shit!
Die!
Just die!
Don't act like you're the victim.
This is your limit, Ja-eun.
You're afraid of me, but you
can't help but feel guilty too.
You want your mom to be happy?
Then, betray your friends.
Those getting the penalty
are Seong Su-ji, Myeong Ja-eun,
Song Jae-hyeong,
and Sim Eun-jeong.
Just so you know,
Ha-rin isn't too
happy with team four.
The black vests.
Pyo Ji-ae?
Pyo Ji-ae.
Wanna trade rooms with me?
I'm not comfortable
with Ja-eun and the rest.
Anyway, the girls whose name
was called, step forward.
Class rep, I think we need
to hold a class meeting.
About what?
Today, we'll be
choosing the F.
-Fs are chosen by votes.
-Our class needs an F.
Didn't you all feel it?
That's the only way to be safe.
You're such a loser.
-Hey.
-Ja-eun, are you listening?
Fuck, look at me
when I'm talking to you.
Where are your manners?
Don't you all feel uneasy?
Not knowing when or who
will fall to that spot.
That's why we'll be choosing
an F among you four.
That's today's penalty.
Who agrees?
Of course they'll
raise their hands.
As long as it's not them.
Safety in anonymity.
Bystanders.
Shin-ye, aren't you
going to raise your hand?
Huh? Oh...
I've been wanting
to talk to you.
The prisoner's dilemma.
Starting now, you will be
snitching on each other's faults.
Like this.
You acted like
you could get rid of the game.
Once you run out of paint balls,
the game is over.
Do your best to come up
with something.
The more you snitch
on your friends,
the more likely you'll survive.
Of course, if you all choose
to keep your mouths shut,
you'll all survive.
But what are the chances of that?
Betray your friends.
BAEK HA-RIN
BETRAY YOUR FRIENDS
What I want?
A rift.
Betrayal.
You guys shattering
into little pieces.
Ja-eun left all alone.
Their faults... Their faults...
What could there be?
Faults...
What faults? Shit...
I betrayed
my friends.
I betrayed my friends.
Hey, are you fighting?
You know,
I was blackmailed
for the first time ever earlier,
by Baek Ha-rin.
But there's something
she doesn't know.
I grew up getting beat up
by my brother.
Bad enough to pop the veins
in an eight-year-old's eyes.
I wouldn't mind messing up
his life a little.
Ye-rim,
will you be okay?
Sim Eun-jeong.
She saw how much I wanted
to make my debut,
but how can she give up on
her own dream so easily?
I can't be friends
with someone like that.
Did you hear that, Eun-jeong?
Have a good life.
I'm sorry.
I heard about your dad.
-It's my fault.
-Ja-eun.
Get your head on straight.
Yeah, let's make
one thing clear.
This isn't your fault.
It's that bitch, Ha-rin's.
What a total bitch.
And you,
don't feel bad.
It's only been delayed, right?
-You're not deleting it?
-That's what I meant to do.
I was scared.
But even so,
we might still
be able to use this later.
I'll talk it over with the girls.
The prisoner's dilemma,
A psychological game where
betrayal makes everyone lose,
but working together
benefits everyone.
Watch closely.
PYRAMID GAME