Im Ye-rim!
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
YE-RIM, WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT? HAHA
See you at the pool.
Ye-rim, you're so pretty.
Ye-rim!
You're so pretty.
Congrats on your debut.
SHIM EUN-JEONG
CONGRATS ON YOUR DEBUT
The 16th Pyramid Game.
Before we begin,
Ha-rin, you have
something to say?
I think we should pick
a permanent F at today's game.
Permanent...
F.
Permanent F.
That person will be an F
until we graduate.
An F until we graduate?
We're playing this
next year too?
-I know.
-One more year.
Does anyone want
to volunteer to be
the permanent F?
Seong Su-ji.
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON THE WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
EPISODE 9
Because of you, Ye-rim...
Ye-rim?
What about Ye-rim?
Ye-rim...
You mean, the sirens
we heard just now?
Are you satisfied?
Because of the game you made,
Cho Wu-ri stays locked
up in her room all day,
Ja-eun slit her wrist,
and Eun-jeong might
not ever swim again.
And now, Ye-rim.
You all know that Baek Ha-rin
is the one who made the game,
don't you?
Go to your seat, Su-ji.
Yes, I made the game.
You'll have to do
exactly as I say from now on.
Like I was saying,
I'll be accepting volunteers
to be the permanent F.
What? Permanent F?
She wouldn't, that dork...
Why do we have to pick
a permanent F?
Rather,
how can you guarantee
that the F will be permanent?
What?
This text.
THE AS WILL SOON BE DECIDING
ON A PENALTY FOR KIM DA-YEON
You failed to penalize Da-yeon
through the game in the end.
So how can we believe you?
That's what
you're basing this on?
Because of that one time?
The only time?
You only got transferred here
a few weeks ago, and you think
you know everything about
the past two years of our class?
I may be the new girl, but I can
still say I don't trust you.
Even if you're the one
who made the game,
this is my game too now.
I agree with Ha-rin.
Park Ji-young, what about you?
Do you agree to
having a permanent F?
Huh?
Oh...
Sounds good to me.
What about you guys?
Yang So-young. Do Mi-yeong.
No.
Don't raise your hand, Ja-eun.
I have to stop this.
Fine, then let's decide
this together.
We'll start with whether
to pick a permanent F or not.
If the girls agree to your
proposal, I'll accept it.
But whatever happens, you
have to accept the results too.
We're all in the game after all.
And I'm going
to put a stop to it.
What?
What about you guys?
Who are you going to pick
as the permanent F?
The friend sitting next to you?
Or behind you?
I don't want to do that anymore.
Because we're friends.
What brings a tower down,
can surprisingly
be a small stone.
Cho Wu-ri.
Myeong Ja-eun.
Sim Eun-jeong.
And Im Ye-rim.
The next
could be any one of you.
Are you still going to play?
If someone
who isn't a lower rank than me,
but an A rank who
everyone looked up to,
someone like Ye-rim, the idol
of our class,
took drastic measures,
this could get through to them.
They'll finally
realize that this game
will destroy not just the F,
but everyone.
Up until now, the game was a
lower version created by Ha-rin,
but looks like
you've found a way.
You and Ja-eun have created
a hybrid version.
If you no longer want to
participate in this insane game,
delete the app and stand up.
If we have a majority,
this game will be gone for good.
If not, we'll choose
a permanent F.
What do you think?
You always said so yourself,
the Pyramid Game
is everyone's game.
Fine, let's do it.
The reason you're so confident
is because of Ja-eun, isn't it?
I'll...
be the F.
Please, just this once.
Don't do anything, Ja-eun.
PYRAMID GAME
I deleted it.
You're not going to make
Ja-eun the F?
The F is going to be Su-ji.
-How?
-Su-ji will never betray Ja-eun.
If Ja-eun volunteers to be the F,
she'll try to stop her.
I want Ja-eun to know
what it feels like
to have a friend
going through hell again.
Since Ja-eun is such a softie,
that'll be much more
tormenting for her.
Anyone else who deleted it?
We need at least 12.
Twelve to be in the majority.
THE PYRAMID GAME
HAS BEEN DELETED
Me.
DELETE THE PYRAMID GAME?
I deleted it too.
PYRAMID GAME
DELETE THE PYRAMID GAME?
Choi Yu-hyun is Baekyeon Group's
scholarship student.
GIRL GROUP TRAINEE
L'S ANTI-FAN ACCOUNT
Choi Yu-hyeon, Joo Seung-ie.
It wouldn't be interesting
without betrayers.
But that means...
DELETE THE PYRAMID GAME?
Huh?
Hey, you guys...
One more.
Just one more.
Please.
Oh well, Ha-rin.
Baek Ha-rin.
I messed up.
Kim Da-yeon,
your vote doesn't count.
What are you even doing here?
-What?
-Ye-won.
Does Da-yeon have access
to the 16th Pyramid Game?
No, she was blocked.
Did you hear that? You're
no longer part of this class.
You're being transferred out
because of your bullying.
Shit.
Hey!
You think you can do this to me?
You don't have enough
votes without me!
We still don't need your vote.
Don't you get it?
You have no right
so stay out of it.
You fucking bitch!
Damn it!
Get off me!
Damn you!
I should've made sure
you'd never walk again
when you were an F.
You fucking bitch!
X GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
CLASS X-X
Hey!
Isn't this class 2-5...
What is this?
You're nothing but a misfit.
Damn it!
What, you bitch...
Shit.
Let go!
Let go, let go!
Bitch!
I'm gonna kill you!
PYRAMID GAME
DELETE THE PYRAMID GAME?
I deleted...
The game.
You still have no intention
of crossing over the line?
The girls have already
started to change.
I know you sense it too.
Then,
at least help within
your little circle.
I'm going to stop the game today.
DAD
PYRAMID GAME
DELETE THE PYRAMID GAME?
PYRAMID GAME DELETED
With the exception of Ye-rim
and Eun-jeong who aren't here,
there are 22 of us.
Twelve for, ten against.
The majority has agreed
to stop the game,
and now,
the game is gone.
X GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
CLASS X-X
JUNIOR CLASS TEACHER'S OFFICE
THE VIDEO HAS BEEN REMOVED
During the live streaming
make sure the video
isn't cut off or removed.
The problem is, the other side
will be monitoring
anything about Kim Da-yeon.
We need a way to keep
them occupied.
The recordings.
Can you post them
with the hashtag "KDY"?
We'll make them focus on that
as we stream the classroom.
JUNIOR CLASS TEACHER'S OFFICE
It's gonna be a shitstorm
after the live stream.
It better be.
There's more to
this than bullying.
There's a reason why Mr. Im
was leeching off class 2-5.
I think Go Eun-byeol,
Jeong Yeon-du and possibly others
were involved in grade tampering.
-Hello.
IM JU-HYEONG,
2-5 HOMEROOM TEACHER
JOO HO-GU
DAEJONG ACADEMY
COLLEGE PREP CLASS
Eun-byeol, is this you?
What?
Where is it?
Dang it...
Why, you little...
Find the camera, now!
Give it to me.
Are you all crazy?
-OMG, what was that?
-Are they all nuts?
-Was that a fake documentary?
-No, it was the real thing.
What game?
Pyramid Game?
-I hope all bullies die.
-Damn, my eyes.
Who's Baek Ha-rin?
She made the game?
My friend went to
the Baekyeon Festival,
and apparently, Im Ye-rim
was taken away in an ambulance.
Baekyeon High School
is in panic mode.
-Why? Is it Kim Da-yeon again?
-See for yourself.
Here's the link.
VIEWS
TRENDING NOW / 1. IM YE-RIM /
4. PYRAMID GAME / 5. BAEK HA-RIN
-Which school?
-Baekyeon Girls' High School.
You had me worried for a sec.
I thought you might volunteer
to be the permanent F.
Yeah, I was going to.
I thought if I just went back
to being the F again,
no one else could get hurt.
But I was wrong.
The game was hurting everyone.
Even Ha-rin herself.
She was actually enjoying it.
Using me as an excuse.
That's why...
I felt I had to stop it.
Thanks.
You set everything
in motion today.
Please leave a message...
Do you know another number we can
call other than Ye-rim's phone?
What are we going to do?
Her phone is still off.
You think Eun-jeong knows?
What happened to Ye-rim?
Is she badly hurt?
Oh...
Um...
Hey.
Eun-jeong, it's me.
Hey!
You better work
super hard at rehab.
Got that?
If you never swim again,
I'm going to kill you myself.
Do you hear me? Eun-jeong!
Hey! Stop!
Hey!
You! You're a stalker,
aren't you?
I saw you on Instagram!
You're a stalker!
Damn it.
Hey! Hey!
Stop right there!
You're hilarious, Su-ji.
So the girls think
something happened to me?
I didn't say that exactly,
but that's what everybody thinks.
Oh my god.
Sorry.
I needed to bluff for the game.
Lee Bo-hyeon and Cha Seon-ju
helped out because of you.
I told you, she's something else.
Bo-hyeon and Seon-ju?
You're not hurt?
I'm totally fine.
The stalker was caught too.
The police called so my mom
and dad went to the station.
It was some woman in her 30s.
Why did my mom make me
so likeable to women?
I'm kidding.
The stalker will be charged
and fortunately, I'm safe.
Those anti-fans
don't scare me a bit.
I did nothing wrong.
Will you guys smile now?
Guys, smile.
I heard you kept your promise
about stopping the game.
I still can't believe it.
It feels a little...
Oh, right. What are we
going to tell our moms and dads?
It's all over the internet.
It's too late to cover it up now.
Just tell them
it's a crazy high school.
You're going home, right?
No, to the convenience store first.
I have something
to return anyway.
Su-ji!
Thanks.
JUNIOR MID-TERMS
PERFORMANCE ASSESSMENT
I copied it from the homeroom
teacher's computer.
I had some time left
and I was bored.
-This is a crime.
-And hidden cameras are legal?
Since when?
Today?
I took a brief look
but there's nothing on bullying.
WOMEN AND MINORS DIVISION
You're here to report bullying?
Do you know
the personal information
of the perpetrator and victim?
Oh, first,
can you tell me your name?
It's Yun Na-hee.
I was a contract teacher
at Baekyeon Girls' High School
until October of this year.
Oh, you have a photo
of your sister, right?
The group photo you
showed me last time.
I don't have that right now.
I have a different one.
But...
Why do you want to see her photo?
That's her.
Wu-ri
was at the school earlier.
What?
Where have you been?
Ye-rim, I'm in Busan too.
This must be fate.
Ye-rim, the lights
in your room just went out.
Good night.
Read the DM.
I told you not to smile
for other bitches!
Why aren't you reading my DMs?
Are you cheating on me?
Just wait.
I'm going to your school.
Cheaters need to be
taught a lesson.
I'm at your school.
But you're smiling
at other bitches again.
Cheaters need
to be taught a lesson.
Be brave one more time, Wu-ri.
Your three o'clock.
I'm watching you,
you fucking bitch.
Remember what you said?
YOU DID NOTHING WRONG
I'LL GET YOU OUT OF THAT ROOM
Ye-rim told me everything.
When you became a junior,
and even though
you were no longer an F,
you got up the courage
to tell the homeroom teacher.
-You did the right thing.
-Because she helped me.
What?
Ye-rim
tried to help me too.
Let's be brave one more time,
Wu-ri.
How's Ye-rim?
She'll be out
of the hospital soon.
Really?
What a relief.
Here.
Can you give this back to Ye-rim?
She dropped it.
Okay.
Wu-ri.
Yeah?
You did good.
Get out.
Get out!
DO-AH
It's me.
Kim Da-yeon!
Kim Da-yeon, you bitch.
where are you?
Find her, quickly.
Bring her to me.
Right now!
A live streaming exposed
bullying at a girls' high school
sending shock waves.
At a prestigious
high school in Seoul,
a junior student was caught
on camera beating up
a fellow student
which was live streamed.
A video titled "High school girls
choosing outcasts by a
popularity vote" May I come in?
The commander...
The video shows students
being exposed to school violence.
A girl punches another girl
not just in the face
but beats her entire body.
The class in the video played
something called the
"Pyramid Game."
Seon-hee.
Doesn't your daughter
go to this school?
Baekyeon Group's school?
This is the school, right?
You can get me transferred
to a new school, right?
It doesn't have to be in Seoul.
Just make sure Myeong Ja-eun
comes with me.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you not understand
what you did?
-You can't?
-Is that what you want?
Mother.
Ha-rin.
I promised you
that I'd give you everything
as long as you
didn't act foolish.
Do you still want to be
transferred out?
Yes.
Your eyes have no focus.
You foolish girl!
Why didn't you tell me?
You told me to learn
how to solve things on my own
if a problem arises.
What?
Okay, just wait.
I'll be there soon.
Su-ji.
If that's what you
call an excuse...
I thought you'd just ignore it
even if I told you.
No, don't report it
to the higher-ups!
Keep your mouth shut.
It wasn't assault.
It's still an accident for now.
I'll do it. I'll investigate
the matter myself.
Calm down and go back to work.
You ignored it.
That was...
I told you to wait!
Okay, just wait.
You're back?
Mom.
Wash your hands.
I steamed some fish
I got from Jagalchi Market.
Let's eat.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
For not knowing.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
HOMEROOM TEACHER'S FILES
Don't go to school today.
In fact, I think you
should transfer.
-I'll go to your school tomorrow.
-I'm okay.
I have friends.
See you later.
Be careful.
-Okay.
-Okay?
What is it?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
See you later.
Did you see the comments?
No.
Seems like the only
thing people want to know
is if I'm a psycho or not.
What do you think?
Stop wrecking yourself.
-I know now.
-What?
What do you know?
That you destroyed
yourself so easily
because I was here.
You're wrong.
You really do
have a bad memory.
You want me to tell you
what you should've known?
No.
I'm not going to use you
as an excuse anymore.
So-eun.
Let's go. Move it.
-Come on.
-Get to class.
Hurry up.
Isn't that the girl
from the video?
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
So many empty seats.
I'm sure a lot of parents
didn't want their kids to come.
Oh my.
Go Eun-byeol didn't even
bother to come?
You girls...
Eun-byeol!
What has gotten into you?
What if I don't get
into a top university?
You have to consult a lawyer
before I get expelled!
Come on!
Geez!
You're impossible!
Get your act together!
What is wrong with you?
We might as well
just die together.
This is all your fault!
Yours and dad's!
Why did you have
to live like losers?
Why did you even have me?
Why?
Why did you make me so ordinary?
This girl.
Send her abroad.
Call Attorney Kim
and get the paperwork done.
Yes, Mother.
Grandmother.
We need an exit strategy.
The lawyers will take care of
the things they can.
But first, the kids...
We can't disgrace
the name of Baekyeon
to protect your daughter.
You're going to blame
my daughter for everything?
Don't worry.
My daughter too.
The school wasn't
aware of anything,
but promises to
deal with it swiftly
and make sure it
doesn't happen again.
Director Choi.
My priority is Baekyeon Group.
Not my daughter.
And certainly not you.
The girls I'm calling
will move their desks to Class 1.
Oh Seong-ah, Myeong Ja-eun,
Shin Shin-ye, and Im Ye-rim.
Next,
Seong Su-ji, Jeong Yeon-du,
Song Jae-hyeong,
Go Eun-byeol, Bang Wu-ie,
you girls are in Class 2.
You're the only one
in another class.
-Will you be okay?
-I'm okay.
Let's have lunch together instead.
Okay.
So, is that video true or not?
We're looking closely
into the matter
and Class 5 has
been reassigned
to prevent this
from happening again.
We'll do everything we can
to sort this out
as soon as possible.
NO ENTRY
Make sure the girls
don't come near this building.
Yes, ma'am.
Aunt.
How much do you have
in your hidden account?
Just be straight with me.
Huh?
I know you've taken
a lot of kickbacks.
Shut up!
Shut your trap!
Argh!
Hey, Ye-rim.
-Ye-rim.
-Hi.
Is it okay to come back
to school so soon?
Yes.
How have you been?
We're in the same class.
Hi.
The traits of organisms
are determined by
the genetic code in DNA.
The genome sequence that
stores the genetic code
are called genes.
In general, genes...
Who knew the cafeteria
could be so loud?
Yeah.
I heard Ha-rin was sent abroad.
-Abroad?
-It didn't cross your mind?
It's a pretty common ending.
She went abroad? So-eun...
So-eun?
I mean, Ha-rin?
If you think about it,
it's the most realistic ending.
I never really thought that
those girls would get
what they deserved just because
the game was exposed.
I wonder what Ha-rin
was really trying to do?
You said you wanted
to tell me something
when the game was gone for good.
Can you tell me now?
Yes.
Where did Ja-eun go again?
We were supposed
to walk home together.
Where's Su-ji?
You're in the same class.
I don't know.
She left on her own.
Guys!
Hey, I have a text.
The girls are coming over.
Why?
I told you to be nicer
to the girls.
Okay, fine.
They read it immediately.
So funny.
Ye-rim!
Hey.
Oh, they felt awkward
and asked me to come
along with them.
Bo-hyeon and Seon-ju
played a huge part,
but Yeon-du...
Oh, oops!
Didn't see you there.
That's blusher on
your cheeks, right?
Your face isn't red because
you're too embarrassed
to face them, right?
Geez, you're so annoying.
-Yeon-du bought this for you.
-Is your leg okay?
Yes.
Geez.
Su-ji and Ja-eun didn't come by,
did they?
Oh, we can't reach them.
Why not?
They're not getting into
trouble again, are they?
You don't think something
is going on, do you?
SKY HOUSE
SEOUL
JECHEON
I'll go with you.
What is it?
When I was in elementary school,
I didn't something bad to Ha-rin.
Something really bad.
SKY HOUSE
BYEON CHO-SUN,
SPONSOR OF SKY HOUSE
Glad you made it.
Remember this place?
FOUNDER BYEON CHO-SUN
"STAY STRONG AND SHARP
TO BECOME GOOD WORKERS"
BYEON CHO-SUN,
SPONSOR OF SKY HOUSE
"STAY STRONG AND SHARP
TO BECOME GOOD WORKERS"
The house.
My house.
Yang So-eun
who used to live here
was bullied.
That's me.
Yang So-eun.
What?
So-eun...
It was me...
PYRAMID GAME