SKY HOUSE
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
MAIN EVENTS IN DECEMBER
CHILD WELFARE ASSOCIATION
DRAWING CONTEST INCHEON
Hi.
I knew you'd come with her.
For a brief second
I thought about giving Ja-eun
a little hope.
So that she'd feel
even more hopeless
after being betrayed by you.
I should never have
brought you into this class.
Whatever.
What is this place?
Why did you tell Ja-eun
to come here?
So that she can see
what happens to me.
What?
Looks like the annex building
at our school, doesn't it?
Do you know what this place is?
Home.
My home.
This is where I live.
Here?
SKY HOUSE
Sky House?
You're the only one I'm telling.
I don't have a mom or a dad.
The little girl, Yang So-eun
who used to live here
was bullied.
That's me.
-Yang So-eun.
-What?
So-eun...
It was me...
What?
Hello, my name is So-eun.
I'm from Korea.
This is my friend, Ga-hee.
She's from Korea too.
Nice to meet you.
Very good.
Everyone, give her a hand!
Isn't Yang So-eun so annoying?
She acts like a princess.
I don't want to play with her.
Don't be like that.
What?
Why not?
-She's my friend.
-You like her?
Who do you think you are?
You're making us look bad.
No...
That's not what I mean.
That's not what I mean...
So-eun...
I feel sorry for her.
Your dad working for Baekyeon
was all a lie?
Heard you're an orphan.
What a liar.
Hey, there's Ja-eun.
Ja-eun, come and play!
Over here, Ja-eun!
Come on!
Ja-eun, let's play.
So, that's why you've
been tormenting her?
No.
-No?
-No.
That's not why.
Is that...?
Oxycodone.
It's okay.
I'll still be conscious
for another five minutes.
Spit it out. What do you think
you're doing? Spit it out, now.
I'll forget what
you did with this.
After all, you were only nine,
and a coward.
Besides,
anyone would have probably
done the same thing.
Then, Ja-eun, what do you think
you did that was so wrong?
Last year, by the stairs
of the main building.
Last year?
Ja-eun, we have
to get out of here.
Come on, let's go.
You. Shut up, and come on.
So-eun!
Fire, fire! Roll out, roll out.
Shinwol-dong orphanage,
Sky House.
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON THE WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
EPISODE 10
I was scared.
The closer I got to you guys,
I was afraid you'd find out.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For not being
just a victim like you thought.
I tried to help Ji-ae
and the others
because of what I did back then.
Because I regretted my actions.
It's okay.
You were only a bystander.
You didn't do
the actual bullying.
And that makes it okay?
I'm not so sure.
Remember what you said?
You asked if it was okay if you
didn't actually hurt anyone.
I'm looking for Myeong Ja-eun...
Ja-eun!
Let me take a look at you.
You're not hurt anywhere?
Look at me.
-Nothing hurts?
-No.
-Really?
-Yes.
I already know
that you leaked this to the press
so don't try to deny it.
How dare you sell out Baekyeon?
Were you always this stupid?
My daughter is about to lose
her spot at the university
both I and her
grandfather went to.
I have nothing to lose.
Don't you understand?
You're not a
priority for me either.
DO-AH
HUSBAND
If this is about the article,
we can talk later...
A fire broke out at Sky House?
Wait.
Who was there?
I'll get back to you.
This is Choi Ie-hwa.
There's something you need
to do for me, Principal Im.
The high school girl "S"
who pretended to be the victim
is currently an arson suspect.
Shockingly, the victim
is believed to be
the heiress of Baekyeon.
When I first saw this video "S"
didn't seem like a victim at all.
It was clear she
had the upper hand.
Honestly,
I could feel her arrogance.
A SCHOOL THAT PLAYS A GAME
TO PICK SOMEONE TO BULLY...
BULLYING GAME, PYRAMID
BAEKYEONG GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL,
SSJ.GIF
Oh, shit.
RANKING 1.
BAEKYEON HIGH BULLYING VIDEO
Deposit confirmed.
I'm posting the article.
UPLOAD
UPLOAD COMPLETE
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
BULLYING WAS THERE EVEN A VICTIM?
BULLYING INCIDENT OVERTURNED?
TURNS OUT THE VICTIM
IS THE HEIRESS OF BAEKYEON?
Yun Na-hee?
Oh!
The contract teacher.
Oh, please.
That woman set up a hidden
camera in the girls' classroom!
She's very dangerous.
The perpetrator?
Actually, I think
everyone is a victim.
I was so stressed out that day
and really scared.
Even my grades dropped.
I heard the school
was transferring Kim Da-yeon out.
She was the problem, not us.
Oh, one more thing.
Seong Su-ji.
Her father is in
the military or something.
Anyway, he came on Parents' Day
and said a lot of crazy stuff.
WHY DOESN'T MILITARY
VIOLENCE END?
FATHER OF STUDENT
AT BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH
INVOLVED IN VIOLENCE AT BASE...
DECEMBER 8, 2023
DECEMBER 9, 2023
SERGEANT MAJOR OF UNIT 6694
"BATTALION COMMANDER
ORDERED INVESTIGATION"
According to tip-offs,
S's best friends are
something else too.
This girl for instance.
She's already famous.
A trainee at Mega.
IM YE-RIM MENTIONED BY "S" IN
VIDEO, YOU WERE A LOW-LIFE TOO
IM YE-RIM'S TRUE COLORS
Myeong Ja-eun had
the worst attitude.
She hardly ever came to class.
And she always looked like
she'd been fighting.
She got a lot of penalties too.
It got so bad I told her not
to hang around at school.
I thought she was the bully.
This is unbelievable.
Can you understand Ha-rin?
I'm Detective Han Ji-min.
We need her to come with us...
What did Ha-rin say?
What did she say
to the two of you?
This is the place.
Where the Pyramid Game
all began.
We are going to play a game.
If you do well,
you'll get a prize,
but if you don't,
you'll get a penalty.
Who do we have to impress
the most when we meet them?
Raise your hand if you know.
Well done.
Thank you.
Eat up.
So-eun, you didn't get
a lot of points at the game.
You won't be getting a blanket
later when you go to bed.
If you don't do well next time,
I'll give that blouse
to someone else.
Do you understand?
That's how
she came up with the game.
FINALS ARE OVER!
STUDY PERIOD!
The cops took Su-ji
away just now.
What the heck is going on?
This lighter is thought
to have started the fire.
Have you seen it before?
Yes, it's Ha-rin's.
Cho-rong.
Isn't this too mean?
Who cares?
She doesn't have a mom
or dad to tattle to anyway.
Right, Ja-eun?
That's what you said.
That she's an orphan.
No...
I just...
-What if I do?
-What?
If I have a mom and dad
can I use this too?
-Oh, that's right.
-What?
Chairman Byeon's son
and his wife in the U.S.
don't have kids.
I think they might adopt
one of the children here.
That would be amazing.
If they adopt, they could
make a huge contribution.
That'd be great.
The Chairman is coming
on Sponsors Day, right?
SKY HOUSE X BAEKYEON
GROUP SPONSORS DAY
Who's the girl
with fire in her eyes?
That's Yang So-eun.
She's in 2nd grade.
Mom!
Mom, can I go with you?
-Look.
-It's Ha-rin.
From now on, if there's
something you want from me,
just ask for money.
Ha-rin, you got it wrong again.
How many times has it been?
GOSPEL OF JOHN
She grew up so fast.
Goodbye.
Get this out of here.
Plant a tree or something.
Yes, Mother.
I'll call the gardener.
It's okay.
If you did something wrong,
apologize, no matter
how late it is.
I'll go with you.
Don't worry, Ja-eun.
Okay.
What?
I'm with my friends.
I'm fine.
Your mom?
Yes, I'll be home soon.
We're all minors here.
No wonder they're worried.
I can't believe Su-ji got
called in for questioning.
Seong Su-ji,
what an extreme life.
What about you?
I'm supposed to go to the
station with my mom this weekend.
Baekyeon is trying to
change the issue.
What if Su-ji ends up
taking the fall for everything?
Don't get me started.
What are we going to do?
Nothing?
Come on, focus!
I choose...
See that woman in black?
Her articles are
all about the facts.
Uh, excuse me...
Are you reporter Kang Seon-yu?
I'm a total fan.
I subscribe to your articles.
Do you want to see?
-Awesome, right?
-Thanks.
You're much prettier in person.
You base your articles on facts.
Hello, I'm Im Ye-rim.
There's something I need
to tell you before it's too late.
I will not be debuting.
I, Im Ye-rim, also took part
in the Pyramid Game that
took place in Class 2-5
at Baekyeon High.
I'm surprised.
I didn't expect you to reach out.
I'm passing the buck to you.
I was on a video call
with my boyfriend
one day in September.
Su-ji, is this really you?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry you had
to go through this.
See?
This is the annex.
Nice building, right?
It's even nicer inside.
My class is in the main building.
-What's that over there?
-Huh?
What?
Oh, it's the girls.
Class five?
I have to go.
What are they doing?
Let's get it over with
before PE is over.
Damn it.
Does it hurt? Does it?
It's your own fault
for being an F.
We could give you a chance.
If you don't like this,
you could take something instead.
An oxy.
LIT TEACHER
Have you seen it?
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Apparently, Ms. Choi
kept that video all this time.
You know, at this point, I'm just
grateful she didn't delete it.
This is the truth behind Class
2-5 of Baekyeon Girls' High.
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
I WAS THE OFFICIAL OUTCAST
OF CLASS 2-5,
A VICTIM AND BYSTANDER
ME TOO
I was also a bystander.
I took part in the game
by being a bystander
to the bullying.
I was a bystander
to the Pyramid Game too.
I WAS ALSO A BYSTANDER
I'm so glad
Su-ji is okay now.
-What about you?
-What about me?
It's not okay for you.
You're really not going to debut?
No.
I've already apologized
to the agency and to the members.
I can't debut anyway.
It all came out.
There, I'm done.
MISS YOU, FRIEND
I'm gonna send a DM.
-To who?
-To my friend.
MISS YOU, FRIEND
What's wrong?
Oh...
Ye-rim...
She called me a friend.
Would that...
For Ye-Ye-rim...
Would that help
-Ye-rim?
-No.
It'd help you.
I read a study
and apparently, sharing
experiences with other people
can help victims
ease their trauma.
I, I'll...
Do it.
You can give it some more
thought before you decide.
It'll be good...
for me, and...
It would help
Ye-rim too.
Ye-rim... She...
She helped me.
She was the only one.
I want to do it.
Seung-hwa.
Then, just remember this.
-You did nothing wrong.
-I know.
I ran into Ha-rin that day.
-What?
-At the festival.
What did you do that to me?
Why was I the F?
You...
Stepped on my foot by mistake.
She said it was because
I had stepped on her foot.
And after I told the teacher,
I was given a penalty,
and had to do a strip show.
I was so scared
they'd post it online,
I couldn't even tell my parents.
Doesn't seem like a lie.
Dang, that's so sad.
Bullied for stepping on her foot
by mistake? That's insane.
She's definitely a psycho.
A strip show?
Are they crazy?
She said Im Ye-rim
was the only one who helped her.
Hang in there, Wu-ri.
We're sorry.
She said
it was because
I had stepped on her foot.
JA-EUN
Hello?
I just remembered.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
I remember now.
The day by the stairs
in the main building last year.
So-eun!
ONE YEAR AGO
It's you, right?
Do you remember me?
I'm Ja-eun, from
Haneulbyeol Elementary.
Myeong Ja-eun.
It's been ages.
How have you been?
How do I look?
You look well.
I'm glad.
I really am.
Ja-eun!
Let's talk more next time.
I'm sorry.
Last year, by the stairs
in the main building.
Last year?
You forgave
yourself for something
I didn't forgive you for.
All the guilt vanished
from your face,
and it made me
want to rip it apart.
That's why I made you the F.
For something you
could never imagine.
I wanted to torment you
until the day you died.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Why? Do you understand me
a little now?
You are one crazy bitch.
-What?
-You heard me.
You're crazy.
Ja-eun.
Am I the only one
disgusted by her
blaming everyone
else but herself?
That's one hell of
a rationalization
and you shifting the
blame makes me sick.
All your self-pity makes me
want to barf.
You know nothing.
Why do I even have to?
Don't pretend
that you've been wronged.
Nothing would've
changed even if she had
gotten down on
her knees that day.
You may have taken an oxy but
at least get the timeline right.
You were already bullying
Wu-ri by that point.
A crazy bitch did
all sorts of crazy shit
and now that
you're backed into a corner
you're saying you
were a victim too?
That's so pathetic.
A victim of bullying?
So?
Does the sob story of being
an orphan and a victim
change the fact that you
played the Pyramid Game?
As Yang So-eun or Baek Ha-rin,
you had a chance.
A chance at redemption.
The person who ruined that
wasn't Ja-eun, but you.
You can't forgive Ja-eun
anymore anyhow. Why?
Because now
you're the bully.
Live the rest of your life
being ashamed of what you did.
That's what Ja-eun
is doing at least.
So-eun.
Even so...
I'm sorry I didn't ask you
to play with me.
I'm sorry
I forgot all about it so easily.
I'm so, so sorry.
Shut up!
I told you,
watch what happens to me.
You'll remember this day
for a long, long time.
What is that?
A fire?
You just can't stop...
Ja-eun, we have
to get out of here.
Come on, let's go.
You. Shut up, and come on.
So-eun!
Anyone here?
Fire department!
Call out!
Hey.
Oh, this?
The test we actually took and the
test that was on Mr. Im's laptop.
Only question 17 is different.
17?
Question 17 was
added later, right?
Class exists everywhere.
School is a smaller
version of society.
In society, different classes...
Would you still say that even
if it makes an F want to die?
I'm saying that it could be
hell for someone.
I think I've found it.
What are you doing?
Su-ji.
Yes?
I saw the interview
one of your men gave.
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood.
Su-ji.
The reason I went to your
school on Parents' Day
was because I was never involved
in your school activities.
You were always so independent,
and dependable.
But before you became
an adult and left home,
I wanted to see...
how you were doing
in your new school,
and meet your friends.
I'm doing well and behaving.
Oh, come on.
Don't worry.
I'm okay now.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I just got a text.
Found the contract.
Your homeroom teacher was nowhere
near qualified to be hired.
Fortunately, the system
kept records of copied files.
It left records of the test
being copied to a
USB stick several times.
Tests being leaked,
and unfair hiring practices.
This will be more than enough.
All we have to do
is raise doubts.
Then, I'm posting this.
Yes.
CONTROVERSIAL BY GIRLS' HIGH
SCHOOL BULLYING +
UNFAIR HIRING PRACTICE
+ TEST LEAKS
Are you okay?
About what?
Don't feel bad.
Bullies are bullies.
By the way,
where did you get
the bullying incident reports?
Reporter Kang Seon-yu?
I'm the one who called,
Yun Na-hee.
I have a lot to tell you
about Baekyeon
Girls' High School.
BULLYING INCIDENT REPORTERS
RESTRICTED AREA IN ANNEX AND HOURS
STUDENTS ASSIGNED
TO CLASS 1-5, 2022
This is finally
coming out into the open.
When did you start planning this?
When you asked
me to keep it safe?
The day you were fired?
I just had a vague idea then...
I see...
I'm sure I disappointed
you that day.
You girls
are so amazing.
I've learned a lot from you.
You're the one who taught us.
You told us not to lose.
That Ha-rin and we
were all just the same
high school students.
I don't know why,
but those words encouraged me.
Thanks.
Now, leave the rest up to me.
This time, I won't let you down.
All right.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
SEARCH WARRANT
We have a search warrant
issued by the
Seoul Central District Court.
Start the search.
-Get all the papers.
-Yes, sir.
Don't forget
the USB sticks either.
Where's Da-yeon?
You piece of shit!
You bitch!
What if she's a psychopath?
Keep it down.
That's why we're doing the test.
You should've known when she
started that nonsense about
going to art school and asking
us to buy designer hand bags!
How dare you come back
to this sacred judo gym?
You were expelled.
That means you're disqualified
from entering
the national competition.
Don't think this is unfair.
You threw away
everything yourself.
Good luck at your trial.
ASSEMBLYMAN
JEONG HONG-GIL STEPS DOWN
DUE TO DAUGHTER'S BULLYING
AND GRADE TAMPERING
This is so unfair!
I didn't do any of the bullying!
But why I am being expelled?
She's a bitch too.
She's just the same.
Her name is Park Ji-young.
She lives in Baneo-dong.
Baneo-dong? Okay.
-Revenge challenge on?
- It's on.
Shit... Damn it...
Then, should I have
gotten beaten up instead?
I'm a victim too.
I did not bully anyone or cheat!
Change the admission criteria
to Hanguk University!
I DID NOT BULLY ANYONE OR CHEAT
NOTIFICATION OF
DISCIPLINARY MEASURES
SEO DO-AH, EXPELLED BASED ON
ARTICLE 17, PARAGRAPH 1-9
It feels weird.
I thought I'd be relieved,
but I don't know...
I just feel weird.
Maybe it's because
the boss is missing?
Baek Ha-rin.
Do-ah?
What are you doing here?
You've been expelled
just like the others.
Are you okay?
It's the consequence
of my mistakes.
Still, in the end,
you stepped over that line.
Thanks for saying that.
Do you like it?
It's my first time
trying something like this.
It's good.
We have to talk.
Why did you do it?
Do you have any idea what you lost
over your pathetic
sense of justice?
Get ready to study abroad.
-Get back on track.
-I'm going to take the GED.
Despite the fact
that my choices of schools
will be limited because of the
red line in my student record.
Seo Do-ah. You shouldn't have
deviated from your position.
-Those are the rules.
-I didn't deviate.
I just have more room
to move now, that's all.
The circle I drew around me
has grown.
And Dad,
I know you saved Director Choi's
number under my name,
and that you're having
an affair with her.
What?
Don't be ridiculous.
What are you talking about?
I think you're the one
who broke the rules.
We never officially
did a psychopath test on her,
but right after we adopted her,
we knew that she was different.
Although we weren't
her biological parents,
we did everything we could
to do our duty.
However, we can no longer
defend her actions
that greatly harm society,
and we're now in the process
of dissolving the adoption.
The truth about her roots
has been disclosed,
as well as the fact that
we're dissolving the adoption.
This time,
I won't act foolish.
WHO WILL SAVE ME
I apologize once again
to the entire country
for these past events.
As a way to to apologize,
Baekyeon Group will suspend
all its work in education.
We will choose a foundation
that can provide
a good environment
and policies...
Drink this.
We hope that this decision
has a positive impact on...
Are you okay?
You look like you have
a lot on your mind.
You never answered my question.
Can you understand Ha-rin?
No, I can't. But...
What I did was wrong.
I shouldn't have ignored
what was happening to her.
Ignore...
I've been thinking.
And I still can't understand her.
I don't even pity her.
She said she blamed you
when you met her again,
but she still made a
game and built a castle
surrounded by bystanders like you.
Ultimately,
it's just the excuse of a bully.
BAEKYEON GROUP'S ADOPTED CHILD
WAS A PSYCHOPATH
I KNEW IT, SHE WAS A PSYCHO
NO WONDER
I GET IT NOW.
SHE'S JUST A DIFFERENT SPECIES
I'M SO RELIEVED
PATIENT
NO FAMILY
That's Ha-rin's punishment.
Indifference and neglect.
She's trapped.
No one wonders about her,
or goes to see her.
From the moment
she opens her eyes,
she'll be in hell.
Right now!
Are you happy?
But...
BAEKYEON GROUP LEAVES
EDUCATION BUSINESS
AND BECOMES LEADING
ELECTRONICS COMPANY
A little more strength.
Yes, slowly.
A little more.
Eun-jeong!
Hey, people might think
we're bullying you.
Move it!
I was...
A bystander too.
2 MONTHS LATER
Hi, guys.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
Wow.
You're not busy?
I'm super busy.
I need a break.
Muscles are the future.
But I can't live without
my bias either.
Gross. Get off me.
I hate it when you do that.
Hey!
That's so mean...
I didn't know you had it in you.
Say that again.
Say it like you mean it!
Just swear!
Winter break is too short.
It's way too short!
By the way, I heard they're
renaming the school.
I'm sure it'll be
something really mundane again.
Hey, Ye-rim, are you sure
about gulping that down?
Don't you have to
watch your weight?
I saw on Mega Hit's homepage
that your members
are debuting next week.
You could start again.
Yeah, I read the comments
and people still like you.
There were only a
few mean comments.
It's okay.
You really won't regret it?
I deserve some sort
of penalty at least.
Even if I didn't do anything,
I may have hurt someone
because of that.
So I just have to deal with it.
I got to perform anyway.
At the festival.
Wasn't I super cool?
You were super cool.
Anyway, we're seniors now.
You just had to bring that up?
You're making me dizzy.
I think I have senioritis.
Wu-ri is prepping for the GED.
By the way,
where's Wu-ri's brother?
He enlisted.
Wanna trade with a gimbap?
Go with the other smurfs.
It's my treat with
my last paycheck.
FREE PASS
Worldly possessions should
be left behind when enlisting.
You're joining the army?
Tell me the truth since I won't
be seeing you for a while.
-You're crazy, right?
-So are you.
Thanks for this.
See you in two years.
-When do you want to go?
-Oh, wow.
Tomorrow!
Let's go tomorrow!
Wow, where did you get this?
-What about cram school?
-Just skip it!
-We have to study!
-Just skip it, skip it!
-That's not important.
-Skip it, skip it, skip it!
-Wow.
Su-ji.
If you run into any problems...
I know, I'll get into
the habit of overcoming them.
You can tell me anytime.
Even if you change
your mind about
transferring schools,
you can tell me.
Whenever.
I'm not going to a new school.
I'm going to graduate from
here with my friends.
See you later!
You're going to be late.
Hurry up.
Hey, you seniors.
Chin up.
Go on in.
And straighten up!
Yes, ma'am!
NEW HEART, NEW MEANING,
NEW NAME, NEW FOUNDATION
WELCOME, MIRYO GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
HARD WORK NEVER BETRAYS!
WE ARE CHEERING FOR YOUR FUTURE
-Hi.
Let's walk over to cram school
together after school.
Are you going to apply for both
liberal arts
and science subjects?
Just liberal arts.
Huh? Why?
Take science classes with me!
Sheesh!
You'll be seeing her
at lunch later anyway.
You can talk then.
Don't make my senioritis
flair up so early in the morning.
It's always the ones
who get low grades
who take 200 extra classes.
Oops.
You're so annoying.
Hey, doesn't Eun-jeong
have a meet today?
Really?
Why didn't you go?
You should go
and cheer her on like this.
I'm your...
I'm...
Your...
Goddess of victory, whoo!
What's up with those moves?
Try this.
Goddess of victory!
Whoo!
How did you do that?
You're awesome.
See you.
Ja-eun, hi.
Hi.
Oh yeah.
I heard the girls from
Miryo Group are coming today.
-Miryo Group?
-The twins?
What are they like?
Who knows?
SENIOR TEACHERS' OFFICE
2025 COLLEGE
ENTRANCE EXAM SCHEDULE
Hey, what was the game
that Baek Ha-rin played
at this school?
HEY, WHAT WAS THE GAME THAT BAEK
HA-RIN PLAYED AT THIS SCHOOL?
The Pyramid Game?
Sounds fun, doesn't it?
Game on?
It's on.
Hi, I'm Seong Su-ji.
PYRAMID GAME
THE 13TH PYRAMID GAME