subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
Because you were the only girl
who opposed to this game.
Right?
This is my plan.
The pyramid?
Fuck it.
Me, become the F?
Interesting idea.
I'll think about it.
What? Did you expect me
to say yes right away?
I may loathe Ha-rin,
but you're threatening me
just like her.
I can't take a gamble
and go all-in with you.
Don't you think?
I can't take it anymore, Su-ji.
Do I have to die for you to stop?
Then, I will.
Please, stop this.
Thanks for everything, guys.
Joo Seung-ie,
come out of there!
Oh no.
Are you okay?
Why did you do it?
You're still bleeding.
Seong Su-ji...
Why did you do it, Su-ji?
You made a mistake this time.
A mistake?
If you turn down my offer,
everyone will know your secret.
You don't want that, do you?
You're the worst.
Are you crazy?
What the hell?
-What did you do to Seung-ie?
-Yeah, what did you do?
Say something!
Are you deaf?
She's crazy.
So shameless.
I believe she's independent,
and conducts herself well.
You have no idea
what's happening at school,
but you simply believe
that everything is okay
with your child?
There is bullying going on
in this class.
Ms. Yun!
Bullying?
I believe your
daughter is a victim.
What do you think
you're doing?
You need to leave.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm Im Ju-hyeong,
the homeroom teacher.
-You can talk with me.
-Tell me again.
Bullying?
If you don't believe me,
why don't you check for yourself?
Su-ji, no excuses?
Why aren't you saying anything?
What did you do to Seung-ie?
She's so shameless.
A mistake...
I don't know.
It looks totally different.
She's putting on a show.
But why?
Why is she putting on this act?
You threatened
the girls, didn't you?
Threats and manipulation
is Ha-rin's specialty.
Besides, your threats are sticks,
but Ha-rin's are
threats and carrots.
You're just a lower
version of Ha-rin.
Then, Ha-rin
can get something on you
and raise your rank?
Raise your rank?
Seung-ie's too?
You have a point.
That was my mistake.
And you used it
to your advantage.
What am I going to do, Ha-rin?
If anyone finds out...
What was your rank again?
I told you you'd find
out soon enough.
You were wrong.
Her act makes me sick.
You're a pyscho, aren't you?
There is more yet to come.
Su-ji.
PYRAMID GAME
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON THE WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
Su-ji.
EPISODE 5
What's going on?
You...
-Is she okay?
-Girls!
Were you fooling around again?
There's no need
to be surprised...
The girls are always...
Mr. Im,
my daughter has been talking
about a new girl making trouble.
Is she a bully then?
How can there be
a bully in this class?
I want an explanation.
Su-ji.
It's nothing.
Su-ji is still new to this class
and this was just a
misunderstanding between friends.
So...
I think it's best
if you let us handle it.
Right, Mom?
Kids have their own
way of doing things.
Don't you agree, Mr. Seo?
C rank Su-ji
harassed D rank Seung-ie,
which led to her suicide attempt.
Only As or those with an A's
permission can mess with Fs.
That's our rule.
Su-ji is not an A
and Seung-ie is not an F.
So this is a disciplinary
committee of sorts.
Then, should we decide
on the penalty first?
Any ideas?
How about we confiscate
Su-ji's votes tomorrow?
All five.
In the 15th Pyramid Game,
-you're not allowed to vote.
-You're not allowed to vote.
What's going to happen to us?
Then the D's alliance...
It's over.
If Su-ji can't vote,
our plan is doomed.
I have to do something
whether it works or not.
Hang on. Before that, Seung-ie,
did I harass you?
How?
What?
You blackmailed me.
I blackmailed you? With what?
Do you have any reason
to be blackmailed?
Don't try to get out of this.
The fact is, Seung-ie tried to
kill herself because of you.
I don't know...
I have no memory of harassing
or blackmailing her.
Do you have any proof that I did?
I just don't get it.
You really are shameless.
She almost died because of you.
Then what about all the girls
who wanted to die because of you?
How about we vote on it?
This class belongs
to all 25 of us,
and we're all in
this game together.
You have it all wrong.
I'm not the one who judges you.
The game does.
This was what you meant?
I gave you a hint, didn't I?
They must be deciding
by majority.
How very democratic.
As expected.
Looks to me that our kids
are solving problems
in a wholesome and sensible way.
A way that's non-violent.
That looks non-violent to you?
I think it looks
like a public execution.
Ms. Yun.
How can we as adults
just look on and do nothing?
If you open that door,
I'll deal with that girl myself.
21 votes.
Su-ji has lost the right to vote
in the next game.
She only lost
the right to vote then?
Does that mean she can still
receive votes?
I'm confused.
This penalty doesn't
automatically make her a F.
She can't vote herself
but she can still receive votes.
Any more questions?
We're screwed.
But Ha-rin...
I'm not done yet.
Have you completely
lost your mind, Ms. Yun?
You're only a temp here!
You had no right!
Please watch your language.
I believe that the
school has aided
and abetted the
problems in that class.
From the students
to the location...
Stop!
Stop talking!
Do you not want to
renew your contract?
It's all over, right?
I'm blocking your number.
You better not
try to blackmail me again.
I'll do what Seung-ie did.
Crazy bitch.
Ja-eun.
I'm sorry.
Huh? For what?
For thinking you were wrong.
Anyway,
we all agree that Ha-rin
put her up to this, right?
Looks like only you agree.
Ha-rin knew exactly
what my plan was
and who I'd approach.
I guess it's not
entirely impossible, but...
I feel like there's
something more...
Your dad...
You said he wouldn't be coming.
Ha-rin was behind that too.
WRITER: WILLIAM GOLDING
THE PYRAMID
PRESENTER BAEK HA-RIN
TEACHER IN CHARGE YUN NA-HEE
TEACHER IN CHARGE IM JU-HYEONG
Why don't we all play a game?
The book we'll be
looking at today
is "The Pyramid," a novel
about England's class society.
Since our parents are here today,
I'd like to ask all
of you to join in.
Use this code
to activate the app.
The adults are playing this game?
Just so you know,
this app is for single-use only
and access will be blocked
automatically in an hour.
Thanks, Ye-won.
What are you up to, Ha-rin?
Basically
this is a popularity vote game.
You just have to vote for
five girls out of the 25.
You can read the details
up here.
Based on the number
of votes you get,
you are ranked from A to F.
Ha-rin.
This doesn't seem
like a very good idea.
Ha-rin,
why don't you continue
your presentation
in the next literature class?
I'm sorry about this.
I'm not the literature teacher
so I didn't know what this class
would be about.
Mother.
What are you doing here?
It's the Chairman.
Isn't that the Chairman?
Of Baekyeon Group.
I'll continue.
Fs
are the lowest rank.
The lowest class,
if we're going by the book.
But...
Why play a game like this?
-Mom!
-What?
Did I say something wrong?
If it's what my granddaughter
wants, we should all play.
Ha-rin must have
a good reason.
Why don't you be a good sport
and play along?
Madam Chairman,
would you like my help
downloading the app?
PRACTICAL EXERCISE
CLASS GAME
1 BAEK HA-RIN
1 KIM DA-YEON
CLASS GAME
The results are in.
CLASS GAME RESULTS A BAEK HA-RIN,
KIM DA-YEON, SEO DO-AH
F...
F SEONG SU-JI 0 VOTES
Seong Su-ji.
Mr. Seong, what do you think?
If one's class was determined
like a pyramid
with a popularity vote
and Su-ji is an F?
Class exists everywhere.
In the military, out in society,
and also...
In school.
When you become adults,
you'll see that
school is a smaller
version of society.
And that in society,
class can lead to law
and order, and that you...
-What is he saying?
-What a boomer.
That's what she had to
put up with growing up?
-That's her dad.
-I know.
Order?
Even if it makes
an F want to die,
would you still say that?
That's just order?
-What do you mean?
-I'm saying
that it could be hell
for someone.
For example...
Someone, who?
Anyway, a game is a game
and this is the result.
The As and F have been decided.
That's a fact.
Right, sir?
Uh, right.
That's what your dad says.
Su-ji, what are you going to do?
This is your little preview?
Because you made Seung-ie
hurt herself,
I've become public
enemy number one
and could go back
to an F at any time.
This is your warning?
And if I don't want
that to happen
I should do exactly
as you say?
This is your plan?
Then...
I'll make the pyramid
come crashing down.
You have a spirited daughter.
Send her to Baekyeon Group
when the time comes.
I'm the Chairman.
Behave yourself.
I believe in you.
Why did you come today?
You never do.
I should've invited my parents
if I knew your
grandma would be here.
By the way...
I heard you recommended Yu-rim
for the Baekyeon Art scholarship.
I'm feeling a little hurt.
I saw you and Da-yeon
sharing looks earlier too.
You don't tell me
anything anymore.
I'm totally disappointed.
Wu-ie.
-Aren't you going home?
-Can you give me a ride?
If you drop me off
in front of my house...
Bye.
Su-ji was going to
get the Ds together.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE,
TOMORROW AT LUNCH...
Yoon Ye-won, Joo Seung-ie,
Ra Hae-jun.
I wonder who gave her the idea?
Who knows?
Hmm.
Do-ah, you used to be so cute.
CLASS MOTTO HAPPINESS
FOR EVERYONE, A CLASS FOR ALL
It was a brilliant idea.
Although, the method you used
was exactly like Ha-rin's.
If I had refused your offer,
would I have been in trouble
because of your threat?
No.
I never threatened you.
You just took it that way.
And I just used how you felt.
I really don't care about your
friendship or whatever it is,
but tell Eun-jeong to be careful
if she doesn't want
everyone to know.
Does that mean you have
no intention of telling anyone?
Why?
What's more interesting than
other people's private lives?
It doesn't matter compared to
the fact that Ha-rin is a psycho.
Do you mean that?
I'm not like Ha-rin.
It's okay, it's okay.
The three of us
will vote for you.
We just have to avoid
being Fs, don't we?
On that note, Su-ji will buy.
Buy, buy, buy.
Cup tteokbokki,
and a hot bar too.
Also, roasted eggs.
21 votes.
Su-ji has lost her right to
vote in the next game.
What's with that look
of distrust on your face?
Ja-eun, she keeps doubting me.
Punch her for me. Make it hurt.
Uh...
I'm gonna go.
My stomach hurts.
Doesn't
seem like number two.
Maybe it's just nerves?
Th-thank you.
-It's past the best-by date.
-Not today.
Hey.
You know the part-timer?
Hang on a sec.
Isn't that Cho Wu-ri's brother?
How did you know right away?
You didn't?
Cup tteokbokki,
a hot bar, and an egg?
Yes, and a chocolate milk.
Ow.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Her bodyguard?
What was that about?
It's all your fault.
What did I ever do to you?
What did I do?
2-5 CHO WU-RI
What did you all
do to my sister?
So the alliance
of Ds is a failure?
What about the camera above
the blackboard?
Oh...
That's okay.
Not that we have
any solid evidence yet.
C-camera?
It's plan B.
I'm gonna get the word out
about this game.
No, what if they do to you
what they did to Wu-ri?
We can't
let that happen.
You and I may be able to take it,
but Ji-ae is going to break soon.
She's going to get
seriously hurt.
Ji-ae...
We need to get
more people on our side.
Not with threats like last time,
but like how you
persuaded Jae-hyeong.
We can't be like Ha-rin.
We have to be more like you.
What are you doing here?
Oh, well...
I was wondering if you
were feeling better.
I bought this at the pharmacy
on my way here.
Wanna sit?
Oh, uh...
I haven't been
on a swing in ages...
I'm okay.
Su-ji isn't a cold person.
She's just really objective.
That's why she can see the pros
and cons of people as they are.
What I'm trying to say is
don't get the wrong
idea about her.
She's on our side.
Su-ji has lost the right
to vote in the next game.
We need to get
more people on our side.
Not with threats like last time,
but like how you
persuaded Jae-hyeong.
We can't be like Ha-rin.
We have to be more like you.
PYRAMID GAME
NOTICE
SEONG SU-JI IS NOT ALLOWED
TO VOTE IN THE 15TH GAME
-Thanks.
-Bye.
Aren't you going home?
I'm not in the mood
to walk all the way home.
I could make you run home
in less than a minute.
The truck stops
at the Bongpo store next.
You'll be able to
get your bag back
if you can make
it there in 5 minutes.
Where are you going?
The police station.
The police station is right
next to the Bongpo store.
Psychos are everywhere.
Darn it!
JOO SEUNG-IE
NEW MESSAGE
Make Ja-eun
the F at tomorrow's game.
MAKE JA-EUN THE F
AT TOMORROW'S GAME
-Got it?
-Yes.
See you.
Bye.
Walking is easier after a run.
Go home, it's late.
I think...
I know what to do.
CHANGE IN CLASS SCHEDULE
2ND PERIOD MATH 4TH PERIOD PE
I'm not like Ha-rin.
See you tomorrow.
Do you really have a way
to bring the pyramid down?
You know how adults played
the game on Parents' Day?
Strictly speaking,
you disclosed our game.
Don't you think so, guys?
Hmm?
We have to break Ha-rin's image
of being an untouchable A.
Don't worry.
She can't come after you
over some pushback like this.
She knows very well
that you have a lot of pull
in this class.
All you have to do is this.
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you overreacting?
Well...
What do the rest of you think?
Who thinks I disclosed the game?
Anyone?
Did your parents suspect?
I guess not, Ye-rim.
Come on.
Who's gonna answer
if you ask them straight out?
They'd be too
scared to say a thing.
Let's do a secret ballot.
Agreed?
It'll be 100% secret, right?
Then, I'm in.
Yeon-du, what about you?
If Ye-rim wants to,
then I'm in.
Does this mean we're skipping
the morning study period?
Yes!
Hey, enough.
Yeah, stop it, Ye-rim.
I just think if Su-ji lost
her votes for breaking the rules,
then the same
rule should be applied
to Ha-rin since that's only fair.
Even if she is an A.
Like you said,
we're all in this game together.
Penalties should be the same
too if you broke the rules.
You're right.
We're all in this game together.
What's going on?
This never happened before...
IN FAVOR 13 VOTES,
AGAINST 11 VOTES
-No way.
-Is this for real?
-You agreed?
-Yes.
Then what comes next?
Forget that I asked you
to become the F.
I want you to become
an A in this round.
With Ja-eun, Ji-ae,
and Jae-hyeong's
votes you can become an A.
If anyone can be Ha-rin's equal
and bring the girls together,
it's you, the idol of class five.
Ha-rin...
PYRAMID GAME / NOTICE /
SEONG SU-JI, BAEK HA-RIN ARE
NOT ALLOWED TO VOTE
IN THE 15TH GAME
Get set.
Vote for Ye-rim later.
Don't vote for me.
I've already told
Ji-ae and Jae-hyeong.
-What? Why?
-Okay, look straight ahead.
I came up with a different way.
I already ran once.
STUDY PERIOD
What the...? What's this?
Ye-rim.
Isn't this about you?
DAUGHTER OF OO FOUNDATION
SUSPECTED OF BRIBING AGENCY...
What's going on?
DAUGHTER OF OO FOUNDATION
SUSPECTED OF BRIBING AGENCY...
CONGLOMERATE BUILDS GYM
FOR DAUGHTER'S SCHOOL?
Oh no.
I know how you hate
this kind of stuff.
Who was it?
Only our class
knew about the gym.
Who was it? Damn it!
I'm Im Ye-rim's classmate.
She's always bragging about
her rich family...
Who was it?
Come clean, now.
Ye-rim's prince is angry.
If that's what friendship looks
like, I don't have any friends.
Don't you think?
Huh?
Ji-young, was it you?
Just kidding.
But you have a big mouth.
Eun-jeong!
Damn you,
Shim Eun-jeong, you crazy...
Have you lost it? Stop.
Don't, stop it.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Stop hitting her.
You've changed, Ja-eun.
Makes me want to break you.
Get out of my way.
Get out of my way!
Don't you think
there's something strange
about Ye-rim's photo?
Looks like it was
taken in this class.
With a hidden camera.
A hidden camera?
Where the hell is it?
Stop it.
I said, stop it!
You were caught
on a hidden camera!
This photo...
THE TRUTH BEHIND "L"
GIRL GROUP TRAINEE...
SHE HASN'T EVEN DEBUTED BUT
HER AGENCY REACHED OUT.
GETTING SUED FOR
TELLING THE TRUTH...
ANTI-FAN ACCOUNT
FOR TRAINEE "L"
This account
belongs to Joo Seung-ie.
Even if I say
Seung-ie is a troll,
no one will believe me.
Has that been
always there?
Apologize to Ji-young first.
If you ever treat
my friends like that again,
I'll never forgive you.
Apologize.
Or I won't ever see you again.
I'm sorry.
But if it really was Ji-young...
There should be
an SD card inside the camera.
We'll be able to know
who put it there.
And who broke
the rules this time.
What was our rule, Do-ah?
"The highest form of penalty
will be applied
if the game is disclosed."
That's mine.
Yours?
This camera?
Yes.
OMG.
I know something
is going on in this class,
and I wanted to know what it was.
I don't believe you.
OMG.
Believe it. It was me.
She installed a camera
to find evidence of bullying?
Who'd believe that?
What was she thinking?
Won't this end her
career as a teacher?
Installing a camera
crossed the line.
It was way over the line.
Totally.
You're honestly going to say
you know nothing
about what's going on?
The end of my career?
You're right, it is.
I'm too embarrassed
to be teacher anymore!
Oh my.
How scary.
Let's get back to work.
Keep it up.
Hey.
FINAL EXAM QUESTIONS
Literature was a shocker,
but Ye-rim and Eun-jeong
shocked me too.
"You were caught
on a hidden camera!"
It was so obvious, right?
100 percent.
I'm not sure about Ye-rim.
She is, for sure.
I just got the chills.
-Doesn't it put you off?
-Yeah.
Are you going to
vote for Eun-jeong later?
I don't know.
Should we vote for her or not?
That camera
wasn't Literature's, was it?
It belonged to Su-ji, right?
Guess her plan failed
since it was discovered.
Oops, sorry.
Did I just hit where it hurts?
Haha.
But did you three
know about the camera?
Where is Su-ji anyhow?
I'm sorry I couldn't
help after all.
If you're here about the
anti-bullying committee again,
then bring me evidence first.
This was written up
in July two years ago.
How could students
be assigned to a class
even before they enrolled
in this school?
Is this the kind of influence
Baek Ha-rin has?
Watch what you say, Ms. Yun.
What do you take this school for?
I've been hearing rumors
about how often she
comes to your office.
If you keep refusing
to answer my questions,
I'll have to report you
to the Office of Education.
Ms. Yun,
the director wants to see you.
You asked to see me...
It was you
who asked me to come?
This school belongs to
Baekyeon Foundation, doesn't it?
I have a question.
Would you like to sit?
Or you can just stand there
as you listen.
Baek Ha-rin.
What's important to you?
Money?
Your job?
Family?
Honor in society?
Usually, those are
what move adults.
Is this a threat?
Your literature class is boring.
You should study more.
Just focus on your classes.
Don't you want
to keep working here?
I'm so embarrassed, as an adult.
I didn't expect an adult
to say that.
I know.
But you know, the camera
was going too far.
What's your plan?
I'm thinking about it.
I may be an embarrassing adult,
but if you ever need help
even from someone like me,
give me a call anytime.
Thank you.
Su-ji!
Don't back down.
You girls don't have to.
To you, Baek Ha-rin
is just another
girl in your class.
Should we report Literature?
Or we can tell the principal so
that she never teaches again...
You're so dumb.
Is that why you
let your dad beat you up?
Oh, wait.
Your brother died because of you.
While in your mother's womb.
Is that when it all started?
The others will laugh
if they ever find out
that at home, you're an F.
That's a mean
thing to say, Ha-rin.
Yeah? So?
Ha-rin knew about it.
Looks like it was
taken in this class.
With a hidden camera.
Only Ja-eun and I
knew about the
camera in the classroom.
What's going on?
Fifth period will
be starting soon.
You told her about the camera,
didn't you?
To Ji-ae.
It was you, wasn't it?
You told Ha-rin.
What?
Why would she?
When Ha-rin brought up
the hidden camera,
only you and Seung-ie
didn't look surprised.
Don't you think
there's something strange
about Ye-rim's photo?
Looks like it was
taken in this class.
With a hidden camera.
You could only react that way
if you knew the camera was there,
and that
Baek Ha-rin knew about it.
Is this true?
Why?
Why did you do it?
Can you really trust her?
Of course.
Why wouldn't we?
If the Ds form an alliance,
our rank will go up...
Are you okay?
Raise your rank?
Seung-ie's too?
There's a camera
in the classroom.
Su-ji thinks you won't be able to
take it any longer.
Ji-ae.
No. I don't even want to know.
I don't want to hear it.
Leave.
And don't
ever come back here again.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
I'm here.
-Hey.
-Hi.
If I'm right, you and Ja-eun...
-Is that good?
-Yes.
-Can I have a bite?
-Uh-huh.
Are you listening?
What did you get?
Anyway...
Su-ji, you're such a klutz!
Me?
Don't fight. I'll clean it up.
Ha...
Nothing has changed.
It has.
At least you have.
As for Ji-ae...
I know.
She just couldn't trust us.
I don't think that's why.
She was friends with
Seung-ie for longer,
and had a moment of weakness.
You and I are so different.
Well, I'm not as strong as you.
When you asked me
not to vote for you in PE...
Your plan was to become the F
and get it all on camera, right?
How did you know?
I've hung out with you long
enough to figure things out.
I would never have
been able to do that.
I'd be too scared.
Now that the camera is gone,
you don't have to go through
with that, right?
This phone has
a voice recording app.
Wu-ri's brother hid it for me.
We've come this far.
You think Plan B
was my only option?
Let's go to class.
Just to remind you,
in this game, Baek Ha-rin
and Seong Su-ji
will not be able
to vote for others.
Keep that in mind as you vote.
Then, let's begin
the 15th Pyramid Game.
15TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
COUNTING VOTES
How much?
15TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
A GO EUN-BYEOL
What the hell?
Why am I a B?
Gu Seol-ha,
are you sure you voted for me?
15TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
B KIM DA-YEON 7 VOTES
Bang Wu-ie, Seo Do-ah!
Damn it.
Park Ji-young!
Fuck this, Yoon Ye-won!
Did you tamper with the app?
Damn it, who was it?
Hell...
RESULTS A BAEK HA-RIN, IM YE-RIM,
GO EUN-BYEOL
CONVENIENCE STORE
SEONG SU-JI 3 VOTES - IM YE-RIM,
MYEONG JA-EUN, SONG JAE-HYEONG
SHIM EUN-JEONG 1 VOTE
D SEONG SU-JI
Myeong Ja-eun...
MYEONG JA-EUN 2 VOTES
Two votes...
Ha-rin, I didn't get
as much votes as last time...
-Did you...
-Stop it!
Are you a stalker?
Will you just stop?
You're seriously scaring me now.
Okay!
Class rep,
did you record everything?
Guys, get together!
INVITE TO GROUP
JAE-HYEONG, JI-AE
Su-ji told you guys, right?
Not to vote for her.
But let's vote for her anyway.
Things have changed now.
It has.
You can say I'm acting
like a goody-goody again,
but we're going to vote for you.
That's what we've decided.
Good.
What?
I was only going to be the F
when there was a camera.
We still have the recorder,
but it isn't visually
effective as a camera.
Becoming the F doesn't
make sense anymore.
So, we're moving on to Plan C.
Ye-rim is going to vote for us.
Jae-hyeong alone isn't enough.
We have to count Ji-ae out now.
Also,
if I'm right, you're
Ha-rin's target.
She wants to make
you the F again.
In order to stop that,
we need someone dependable
in addition to you, me,
and Jae-hyeong.
And that's Ye-rim?
I told you to be careful
about Eun-jeong.
Keep your distance for a while.
How?
Hint to your other friends
to drop Eun-jeong's rank.
That way, people will stop
doubting you for
what happened today.
And it's better
for Eun-jeong that way too.
And?
Like I said,
the girls will vote for you.
You vote for me,
Ja-eun, and Ji-ae.
Let's do away with the F.
I lost?
To you, Seong Su-ji?
This is just the beginning.
It was a mistake
keeping Su-ji close to you.
Let's stop this, Ha-rin.
Stop doing this to the others.
The more you act
like this, you...
Then why did you do that to me?
You did it to me too.
You've been wondering,
haven't you?
Why you've been the F.
Seong Su-ji.
Well, that was quick.
And you didn't know
anything, did you?
Clueless as always.
It was because of Ja-eun.
The reason you were an F.
It was because of Ja-eun
that I was an F?
So all that bullying
was because of her?
That's bullshit.
Why was that because of her?
It was because of you.
Ra Hae-jun, Joo Seung-ie,
Pyo Ji-ae, me,
and Myeong Ja-eun...
You assigned girls from ordinary
and average
families into this class.
Girls with weaknesses
and easy for you to handle.
Then, what is Ja-eun's weakness?
I wondered for a while.
I don't know what
kind of dramatic
past you and Ja-eun share,
but I'm on to you now.
You want to keep Ja-eun
as an F, for always.
And if I do?
Ja-eun, you answer.
Do you want to stay as an F?
No.
I don't.
PYRAMID GAME