14TH PYRAMID GAME RESULTS
COUNTING VOTES
subtitles for the platform @mkdoramas
SEONG SU-JI 5 VOTES
What...
Why am I a C?
Five votes?
Then what about Ja-eun?
MYEONG JA-EUN 2 VOTES
Someone voted for us.
But who?
What is it?
PYO JI-AE 0 VOTES
Why is Ji-ae an F?
This wasn't the plan.
That means...
PYO JI-AE 0 VOTES
Not me or Ja-eun, but Ji-ae?
SEONG SU-JI 5 VOTES
Who voted for me?
I don't know what's going on
but for now...
This is good.
You and I got out of it.
But why...
Why Ji-ae...
-What happened?
-It's obvious, isn't it?
She had a falling
out with her bestie.
That must've been the reason.
Did Da-yeon rough you up a lot?
I'm so mad.
This is the Fs fault!
One of them realized
that even best friends
can turn on each other.
I told you it'd be easy
to come between them.
To sum up,
Seung-ie got herself new friends.
And Ji-ae lost her only friend.
REFRESH
RECOUNTING VOTES
Seung-ie.
You didn't vote for me?
She crossed the line.
Myeong Ja-eun got two votes?
Since when did she play?
She must've gotten ideas
because of the new girl.
What should we do
about this, Ha-rin?
Wu-ie, what are
you talking about?
Why are you asking me?
Huh?
Seung-ie, how could
you do this to me...
Seung, come on.
We're going to the restroom.
You're talking to an F?
No.
What can we do
to help Ji-ae?
Any ideas?
If the three of us
refuse to play...
-You liar.
-What?
I have a rough idea
of who you are now.
You're...
You're trying to pull out,
aren't you?
Stop trying to come up with
an excuse. I know you.
You don't care anymore,
is that it?
She can be smart
when she wants to be.
You know,
I'm not a good person like you.
I'm very ordinary.
This game? I wouldn't have
even cared if I hadn't been an F.
So, why should I help her?
You're an F!
Don't talk to her.
Let's go.
She was self-centered
and so am I.
That's not a crime.
You said you wanted
to destroy the game.
Everything you just said
is an excuse.
Making excuses won't change
a thing. I know.
Keep your promise, Su-ji.
You said
you wanted to change this class.
Ja-eun. I'm sorry.
Things are different for me now.
I'm...
no longer an F.
PYRAMID GAME
DOWNLOAD PYRAMID GAME APP
I AGREE TO THE RULES
BASED ON WEBTOON
"PYRAMID GAME"
PYRAMID GAME
EPISODE 3
Congratulations, Su-Ji.
I know it was rough.
Even though it wasn't your fault.
That won't happen again.
I'll help you out this time.
Help me?
No, wait. I'm a C.
My rank is a C now.
It doesn't matter if she's
the ringleader or a psycho.
I don't have to be
hostile to her anymore.
Thanks.
I feel much better hearing that
from someone who's always an A.
You're the first person
who jumped up two levels
from an F.
Damn, I got an F all over my shoe.
Thanks.
Stop it, Da-yeon.
Do-ah...
Did you forget the rules?
Hazing the F starts the day
after the vote.
Recess is over.
Go back to your seats.
I'm paying you back.
That'll be 2,200 won.
This one is five minutes past.
PYRAMID GAME
This is Yu-rim. I'm inviting
you to the B-D group chat.
Want to go to school
together tomorrow?
Morons.
School friends?
Just classmates.
Thanks for the invite.
Girls like this are
sneaky and selfish.
But starting today,
I'm no different.
Why?
Because it's safer that way.
Then, who is in danger
instead of you?
Hello.
Wow, it's Su-ji. Congrats
on joining the group chat.
Actually, I've been wanting
to be friends with you.
"A guilty conscience
pricks the mind."
That's how the saying goes.
Who said it was because
a guilty conscience
is shaped like a triangle?
But for some guilty consciences
the pointy ends are so worn down
that they became a circle.
So it doesn't hurt
even if you're pricked by one.
Su-ji, hi!
We said hi on the group
chat yesterday.
Your bangs are so cute.
Where did you get your hair done?
I'm sorry about
the other time.
Let's make up.
You're not the type
who holds a grudge, are you?
F, who are you going
to vote for today?
Hey, F!
It's okay, I was an F then.
Wow, Su-ji, you're more
easy-going than I thought.
I know. So cool!
Totally my style.
What are you looking at?
Oh, Ha-rin?
I heard she's not
coming to school today.
Oh...
SKY HOUSE
Come play with us!
Show me your hand.
SKY HOUSE &amp; BAEKYEON GROUP
PATRONAGE DAY
Thank you.
What's your name?
It's Ah-yeon.
Oh, what a pretty name.
Ha-rin.
Doesn't she look just like you
when you were little?
What do you think?
I don't know, Mother...
Excuse me, I have some
business to take care of.
So foolish!
At work and at home.
Ha-rin is so much prettier.
I'm not saying that
just because she's my daughter.
She is pretty.
That's why I renovated
the entire school
to be ultra-modern
as a gift when she started!
That school is yours
until the day you graduate.
Do everything she wants for her.
That's why I made you
the director of that school.
Of course.
I'll take very good care of her.
I love you, Grandma.
I love the school.
BAEKYEON GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Oh, hey Su-ji.
-Hi.
Oh, you go ahead.
Thanks.
Su-ji, that time I...
Fuck off.
SEONG SU-JI 5 VOTES,
MYEONG JA-EUN?
MYEONG JA-EUN 2 VOTES,
SEONG SU-JI?
How's school?
-Are things okay?
-Yes, I moved up a level.
In the mock SAT test.
I think I'll be able to
maintain my level in school too.
Grades aren't everything,
you know.
Schools...
Are a smaller version of society.
Yes.
So be good.
And if a problem arises
work it out and get through it
instead of trying to avoid it.
No, Dad.
I'm going to avoid it.
I'm going to do all that I can
to avoid it.
What are you doing?
What's so funny?
Ha-rin, listen to this. It's...
When you see the others
watching you get bullied,
don't you just want to
dig their eyes out?
They'll never know
the look in their eyes
when they look at the F.
What is that?
Are you not friends
with Ja-eun anymore?
That's too bad.
I voted for you two.
You voted for me?
-Why?
-Just because.
You don't believe me?
Then who among the lower ranks
do you think voted for you?
Let's say you did.
Why did you help me?
Is there something you want?
Wow, quick reaction.
You're funny.
Something I want?
I'm not sure.
Not really.
Ye-rim.
What's taking so long?
What are you doing with her?
Me? I'm a C like you.
Just kidding.
Anyway, thanks, Ye-rim.
She's not wrong.
The lower ranks have to give
any remaining votes to As or Bs
in order to keep the others
of similar rank in check.
Forget about the lower ranks.
Who among the As or Bs
would vote for me?
And why?
I'll get going then.
It almost flew off.
Let's move if you're done.
In the second semester
landscapes will count for 50,
and emoji designs another 50
for a total of 100.
You all know this, right?
Landscapes will be
relatively evaluated by you.
What's this?
With full marks being 50,
deduct five points each
to 45, 40, with 30
being the lowest score.
I'll be grading
based on your evaluations.
Focus on composition
and presentation.
Class rep, hand these out.
You'll be more at ease
without me around, right?
Mark them and bring it
to the office later.
Be good.
ART CLASS (LANDSCAPES) GRADES
You want the students
to evaluate each other?
Ha-rin wanted me
to give you this.
Baek Ha-rin...
BAEK HA-RIN 50
Mr. Im said this was
a relative evaluation,
but why don't we go
stand by the score
that we think we should get?
What?
What's going on?
Let's go.
Come on.
I'm a 35...
But this is included
in our school grade...
Hey.
Come on, we're 45.
But Yu-rim,
aren't you on an art scholarship?
Huh?
No, this is where she should be.
We all promised.
This is where we all should be.
Right?
Ye-rim, what do you think
you're doing?
You think Cho Yu-rim's
drawing is good?
Yu-rim, say something.
Is that what you think too?
She does.
No.
I should be here.
Liar.
Wait a sec.
Cho Yu-rim, Ra Hae-jun are Ds.
Park Ji-Young is a C.
Im Ye-rim, Jeong Yeon-du are Bs.
Baek Ha-rin, A.
They're standing by rank.
A, B,
C,
D,
F.
Su-ji.
Don't just stand there.
Come over here.
How much does the ranks...
the pyramid, affect this class?
Nobody is threatening them
with a knife,
but they're willingly tanking
their school grades over this?
How bizarre.
So bizarre.
Am I really okay with this?
Woah, I was almost late.
Hi.
We'll now being
the 15th Pyramid Game.
SEONG SU-JI 0 VOTES
SEONG SU-JI 5 VOTES
I'm not okay.
I need to know
where I got the four votes.
IN CHARGE OF HANDING IN PAPERS
SEONG SU-JI
Guys, hang on a sec.
I have a suggestion to make.
The good thing about
getting a higher rank
is that it makes it possible
to stir things up.
This voting system with the app...
Don't you think it's
a little weird?
What? What are you
suddenly talking about?
What's weird about it?
Are you just being a troll?
You never thought
there was something off about it?
Not even once?
I heard the results
were almost always the same.
Especially with the As.
Am I the only one
who thinks it's weird?
You never suspected
that it could be tampered with?
Wait, Su-ji.
The app is totally reliable.
I made the app myself.
If anyone tries something,
it shuts down immediately.
Well,
what if you're a part of it too
as the developer?
How can we trust it?
Do you have any proof that
it's never been tampered with?
-OMG!
-How about we vote the old way?
We can write down the five names
we voted for in the 14th game
and count them to make sure.
Of course, it'll be anonymous.
I'm in.
Ye-won, what about you?
Okay, fine.
You're accusing my baby
of being tampered with?
Su-ji, I'm disappointed in you.
You've insulted me.
If it was rigged, would I be a D?
Fine, let's do it.
Sounds fun.
If it's anonymous...
Honestly,
I did have my doubts.
How can I be a D?
Everyone thinks you're a D.
I'll count the votes then.
SHIM EUN-JEONG.
JEONG YEONG-DU,
MYEONG JA-EUN,
SEONG SU-JI, BAEK HA-RIN
Hey, it's exactly the same.
Wow, so lame.
Su-ju was just trolling?
See?
My baby is totally innocent.
Yeah, I'm sorry I doubted it.
I apologize.
Thanks for
participating everyone.
I'm on my way to
the teacher's office.
Did everyone hand
in their assignments?
You all did, right?
Then, I'm handing them in.
There was no twist after all.
This isn't a movie.
It's real life.
BAEK HA-RIN, KIM DA-YEON,
SEO DO-AH, BANG WU-IE, GU SEOL-HA
SHIM EUN-JEONG, JEONG YEON-DU,
MYEONG JA-EUN,
SEONG SU-JI, BAEK HA-RIN
You all did, right?
Then, I'm handing them in.
If I compare the handwriting,
I'll be able to figure out
who voted for whom.
KIM DA-YEON, BANG WU-IE
BAEK HA-RIN
I expected as much,
but these three
really voted for me?
I'm no longer an F
because it's what Ha-rin wanted?
If that psycho changes her mind,
I can always become an F again.
Damn it.
There's no guarantee they'll
vote for me again
in the next game.
What about Ye-rim?
She really voted for me
and Ja-eun this time.
She could vote for me again.
Yeah right.
Draw some dimples too.
Wow, so pretty.
Ji-ae, you are too cute.
Good girl.
That's right. Good girl.
Eat up.
-This?
-Animals can't talk.
That's enough.
That idiot.
She just can't stay out of it.
Unbelievable.
What do you think you're doing?
You're a D now, is that it?
Da-yeon, what do you
want me to do?
Ja-eun, Myeong Ja-eun...
Do you want to take her place?
You instead of Ji-ae.
You do whatever you want.
Give it to me.
Ja-eun, don't.
You can't do this to her.
Apologize.
Now.
BAEK HA-RIN
Oops, I missed.
I was aiming for Ja-eun.
I'm sorry, Ha-rin.
Are you okay?
I'm really sorry.
Why are you butting in,
you dummy?
You're too nice for
your own good.
-Crazy bitch, are you insane?
-Are you talking about yourself?
Do I still look like an F to you?
Yeah, so? I'm a B.
Only As or those with their
permission can mess with Fs.
Those are your rules.
And as you can see, I'm not an F.
And you're not an A, Wu-ie.
Let her go, Wu-ie.
Su-ji said it was a mistake
and apologized.
Let her go.
You're pretty smart, Su-ji.
Yes, I am.
And Ja-eun,
-I'll keep my promise.
-Promise?
Ja-eun and I agreed
not to bully the F,
I mean, Ji-ae.
Oh, is that okay?
Everyone seems to take
cues from you.
You must've gotten
the wrong idea.
There's no need to ask me.
I'm just one of the 25.
And you're one of us.
I'm not the one who judges you.
The game does.
Girls, I'm putting up
the literature...
What's with this mood?
Is something going on?
I'll put it up on the board.
Are you fighting?
No, we were just
in the middle of a game.
Next time,
just ask me to come.
You don't need to come here
during recess or lunch time.
All the other teachers do that.
Good luck, Su-ji.
Thanks, Da-yeon.
Damn it.
Oh.
Hey, give me your number.
Ah, it's been a while
since I've acted on impulse.
I had a feeling you'd be here.
I was wondering if you're okay.
Su-ji, if you're forcing
yourself to keep
your promise because of me...
Do you have an overinflated ego?
I thought you knew me.
You think I'm someone
who'd do this for you?
I'm doing this for me.
Ha-rin voted for me.
Ha-rin?
-How did you know?
-You don't need to know how.
I've concluded
I'd rather destroy
the game then
end up as an F again
while getting jerked around
by that psycho.
So, this is just a deal.
Let's do this.
For real this time.
What's Ji-ae doing?
Stop crying.
That's enough.
We've had it just as bad as you.
What? I'm not like you!
This was the first time anything
like this ever happened to me.
I was so scared.
My best friend betrayed me,
and I practically lost it.
How could Seung-ie do this to me?
But you!
How can you be so mean
to someone crying?
Don't you know how
to relate at all?
Are you some kind of sociopath?
You know, I feel sorry for you.
Seung-ie is a total bitch.
I don't want to ignore what
Da-yeon was doing it to him.
Best friends should
try to understand...
Come to think of it, betrayal
is written all over her face.
If she had been born 100 years
ago, she'd have betrayed...
She's mental, scum. She's like
the devil, sneaky as hell.
Okay, that's enough.
Then, should we keep talking?
-Su-ji.
-What?
You're so weird.
The class wasn't always this way.
There were more well-to-do
girls than most,
but the class atmosphere itself
was pretty ordinary.
But then...
1 YEAR AGO
Class rep, we're bored.
How about we all play a game?
That's how it all started.
Kim Da-yeon?
Not Baek Ha-rin?
Ha-rin?
No, Ha-rin did nothing...
She just looked on.
Vote for the girls
you felt grateful
for during the past month.
The girls who get the most votes
will get a small benefit.
Not being on class duty
during exam periods.
Getting to choose the order
of performance assessments.
Getting to eat first
during lunch.
The benefits gradually changed.
It's Day 1 today.
Oh no.
Poor thing.
-Are you okay? If you curl up...
-Stop being such a pain!
I'm sorry.
The benefit to look down on girls
who were of a lower rank.
That's when the mood shifted.
There was discrimination,
and violence...
Hang on a sec.
These weren't the rules
to begin with,
but it evolved as you went?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, just naturally.
Being a monster rubs off.
"Being a monster rubs off."
Anyway, for a while
in the beginning,
you could bully anyone if they
were a lower rank than you.
And then...
The rank F was created.
What are you staring at?
Hey, F!
I'm sorry about swearing
at you earlier.
I apologized, okay?
The rule was made
that Fs were outcasts
and could only be bullied by As
or those with their permission.
There were no restrictions
about leaving a mark back then.
So, who was it?
CHO WU-RI 0 VOTES
Cho Wu-ri?
She's the one who was always
the F in your sophomore year?
What happened to her?
I don't know.
I don't think she was an F when
she moved up to the 11th grade.
But she dropped out a few months
before summer break.
YOUNGER SISTER
That's why they reassigned
the class numbers?
To delete she existed.
The video you showed me...
You got it from
someone too, right?
I'm sorry I didn't thank
you earlier.
I heard you're the one
who sent it to Ja-eun.
The video.
That's an edited version.
Only the As have the original.
Why did you help me?
"The highest form of penalty
will be applied
if the game is disclosed."
Why do you think
that condition was added?
For justification?
Not that it does any good.
You guys do whatever
you want anyway.
You're right.
I just thought
the justification was weak.
And I didn't want to see anyone
else's clothes get ripped off
just for that justification.
That's why you tried to keep me
away from the homeroom teacher?
Then what about during
the written vote?
You know I took them.
I did think it was careless.
I knew you wouldn't mention it
to anyone.
I heard you're the one who
came up with the rules for Fs.
Stopping when the bell rings.
That's to stop it from getting
out of hand.
Hazing begins the day
after the vote.
That's to prevent the F
from getting hurt too much
since everyone is too
worked up on that day.
-So?
-Will you help me?
I want to form an
alliance with the Ds.
Of course I'll help out
with the school board.
Principal Im will feel at ease
with you in charge.
Do-ah cares about
Ha-rin very much.
We parents should help
out in anyway we can
so that the girls
can build up trust.
They'll be friends
for life after all.
This time...
You're really sloppy.
I must have overestimated you.
-What?
-Why do you think I'll help you?
I don't have a reason to change.
And I have no intention
of undermining my position,
my power, or my relationships
based on mutual trust.
The rules?
The rules are there
to protect myself.
I don't ever leave
the circle I drew around myself.
That's my rule.
Rules, rules.
Rules are all you care about?
So you're saying
you won't help me?
-Ever?
-Ever.
You should be more careful.
An alliance with other Ds?
How many Ds do you think
have no connection
to the upper ranks?
I'm not sure if you'll be able
to convince them so easily.
After all, compared
to the upper ranks,
you don't have a lot
to offer the Ds.
How many Ds do you think
have no connection
to the upper ranks?
That means there are a few.
What? I thought she wasn't
going to help.
The one girl who was opposed
to the game in the past.
Maybe she was talking
about herself?
Hey, Do-ah.
What, those two?
What were they doing together?
She's a D, right?
Her family
owns Palm New Chemistry?
Yes, I heard in the restroom.
Stop pushing.
PALM NEW CHEMISTRY
QB GROUP ACQUIRES
LOOKING FORWARD TO SYNERGY
-So this is why.
-Huh?
I've been thinking
it was strange.
Why were the girls not
in the upper ranks
going along with the game?
They can't fight back because of
how their parents are connected.
The new girl.
What was her name?
Seong Su-ji?
Eun-jeong,
I know you couldn't care less
about other people
but try to learn her
name at least.
She's in our class.
You like her, don't you?
I can tell.
She's different.
Who else would provoke
Ha-rin like that?
Stop.
Just ignore her.
What?
Are you jealous?
Geez, are you nuts?
Oh my god.
You scared me.
You totally scared me.
I've never been here before
on a day off.
No one else is here. It feels
like we rented out the place.
Well, it is yours anyway.
I told you not to
talk about that, Yeon-du.
What brings you here?
I dropped by
on my way to clubbing with her.
Did you hear that our next
meeting is in Kota Kinabalu?
A night on a yacht.
With our parents.
Where's the fun in that?
Can you get to the point?
I need to study.
Such a straight-A student.
You do know that only
you, me, and Ha-rin
will last after graduation?
The other relationships
won't last.
We can't betray each other.
Whether you and I like it or not,
we have to see
Ha-rin our whole lives.
You're right. We'll never
be out of each other's lives.
-Exactly.
-But I'm not like you.
I don't play the game
because I want to.
I'm only doing what I can.
Thinking about it
makes me so mad again.
Always acting all snooty
and neutral.
You picked her
to be the game host
and she thinks
she's something.
Seo Do-ah better not betray us.
I'll make her regret it.
-Wu-ie.
-Yes?
Do you want me to
buy you this painting?
This?
Looks super expensive.
You have to do
something for me though.
What is it?
I'm happy to do anything for you.
Then...
Can you please...
know your place?
Wu-ie, all her life,
Do-has been taught
to hold on to the power she has,
and her position
and the connections
based on trust.
Do you know what that means?
I overstepped.
I crossed the line.
Why would Do-ah betray you?
You and her are friends.
Friends?
Is that what a friend is?
-A game?
-Yes.
1 YEAR AGO
I want a hierarchy in the class.
Like a pyramid.
Doesn't it sound fun?
We could decide our ranks
through a game.
Do-ah, what do you think?
Do you want to go ask your dad?
You're a good girl who always
listens to her dad, aren't you?
How are you going
to destroy the game?
With an alliance of Ds.
We can use the
desire to level up.
We'll get the Ds together
and make them all a C.
What? Me a C?
That got you interested, right?
That's the desire to move up.
No human is immune to it.
One person gets five
votes each, right?
I ran the numbers and the C
who had the least votes had five.
If we get three more Ds to
join us and vote for each other,
we'll all get more
than five votes each.
That'll make us all Cs.
Cs.
That'll make a total of 11 Cs.
There'll be more Cs than Ds.
Like this.
The pyramid will fall more
easily than we think.
If the Pyramid Game is no longer
shaped like a pyramid,
the game will be over.
So, my point is,
we have to get together
the Ds who'll move up
to being Cs with us.
Which three among the Ds?
Yeah, I'm wondering myself.
How do we find the girls who have
no ties to the upper ranks?
I don't know the girls that well.
Me neither.
Mr. Kim. I'm here on an
errand for Mr. Im.
Could you open
the cabinet for me?
Oh...
-Tidy up before you leave.
-I will. Thank you.
Yesterday was the last day
to finish up transcripts.
And Mr. Im was absent.
It was total chaos in the office.
I told Math I was doing an errand
and asked him
to open the cabinet.
Wow.
You really are
something else, Su-ji.
You're such a great liar too.
It's not that hard.
You just need to think quick.
It's easy when it's critical.
Sometimes...
You remind me of someone.
The way you think and act.
Who?
Whatever, it's easy
to tell now, right?
Tell what?
Homeroom wrote everything
we need to know in his notes.
I'm only going to
explain this once.
First of all, the Cs.
Ji-young's parents work
at Baekyeon Food
so she's connected to Ha-rin.
Seon-ju's dad owns SJ Company
which is a subcontractor
for Da-yeon's family.
There are more like them.
It's not important
so I'll move on.
Now for the Ds who
are important to us.
Yang So-young's parents are
doctors at Seosim Hospital.
Choi Yu-yeon gets a scholarship
from Baekyeon Group.
If we exclude everyone like them,
that leaves six Ds
we can approach.
Yoon Ye-won, Go Eun-byeol,
Cho Yu-rim,
Ra Hae-jun,
Song Jae-hyeon, Joo Seung-ie.
We just have to
pick three from them.
But not Go Eun-byeol.
She's crazy and
a pathological liar.
Not Joo Seung-ie either.
Wow, so this is C programming?
I've never actually
seen it before.
Are you writing malware?
No, this is just a hobby.
What?
You're suspecting
me of tampering again?
No, we proved that
the game was clean.
Let's be cool, buddy.
I'm analyzing code.
Why, are you interested?
Can you tell the difference
between a hacker and a cracker?
Wow, my pride just took a hit.
Communicate through text only.
For now, Ja-eun and I have to
mingle more with the others.
That way,
we'll get an opportunity
to bring them over to our side.
Hey, It's Shownu X Hyungwon.
They're live streaming
was awesome yesterday.
I love how Shownu dances.
You're a MONBEBE?
-You too?
-Me too!
Have you ever been
to their fan sign event?
Yes, of course.
-Really?
-You've never been?
So cute.
Huh?
Hey.
Who are they? They look funny.
What? Why are you picking
a fight over my boys?
Ye-rim, need this?
Oh, thanks.
-There's one more, right?
-There is.
For the second step,
whatever happens to Ji-ae,
we have to ignore it.
What? Why?
Then,
what am I supposed to do?
We're in this together.
We can't draw
any more attention to ourselves.
Make it look like we went our own
ways after trying to resist once.
MYEONG JA-EUN - OKAY
Ja-eun, are you making fun of me?
Wow.
-I got Dragonite.
-Huh? Can I have it?
This is for Ra Hae-jun.
I need it to strike up
a conversation naturally.
Hey, this is good!
It's good.
Come on out.
Hang on,
you better not ruin it.
Don't worry.
I'll save you 5,000 won.
Cut it like mine.
Absolutely not.
-Come on, just once.
-Don't cut it like Yu-rim's.
I'm cutting it for real now.
-Su-ji is good at this.
-Your turn now?
Yes!
Hi, nice day today.
"Hi, nice day today."
You sound like a robot.
Try to smile a little.
You look like Joker.
Don't smile. Just say this.
"Wanna go for malatang later?
It'll be on me."
-Malatang?
-Just repeat after me.
"Wanna go for malatang later?
It'll be on me."
"Wanna go for malatang..."
Wait, Ja-eun.
I can't help but feel
something is going on.
You can talk to me.
Is anyone being bullied
in your class?
Well...
Uh...
Actually...
Hello.
Oh, Ha-rin.
Ja-eun, aren't you going to
change into your gym clothes?
Do-ah will lock the door again
if you're late.
Oh, right. Go to class.
We'll take this up
again next time.
You look tired. Is something up?
So, you've competed
at international
anti-hacking competitions?
Wow, I'm impressed.
By the way, how did you end up
making the Pyramid Game app?
I offered to make it.
Writing the names
and counting the votes by hand...
How primitive is that?
You offered?
But you're...
Oh...
Never mind.
What?
Bang Wu-ie who only drew
the logo is a B but I'm a D?
A sense of inferiority.
Being a D despite
creating the app...
There's a 99% chance
she's unhappy.
No, 100%.
Were you going to tell her?
To the literature teacher?
No, I would never tell.
I was only going to tell her
not to worry about anything.
Why?
She could be able to help.
It would only make things worse.
You wouldn't want
an anti-bullying
committee to be held.
You're worried about me?
In case I got into trouble?
Thanks.
But, then why?
Why did you get out
of being an F?
How dare you?
Why did you trade votes
with the new girl?
Hmm?
Ja-eun.
You know you can't do this to me.
NAME: YOON YE-WON
"Has a lot of pride
and the desire to be recognized.
Hates to lose,
but tends to comply
when it's to her benefit.
Seeks practicality
in friendships as well."
HOW ARE THINGS GOING?
COME TO THE ROOFTOP
What? She read my text
but why isn't she coming?
What's wrong?
You look frozen.
Huh?
I'm fine.
How's the plan going?
Ji-ae keeps texting.
Oh...
PYO JI-AE
DON'T DO THIS TO ME
SEONG-MYEONG-PYO
HEY
I don't have enough info
on the girls.
Info...
It'd be simple if we could
hack their phones.
Hack?
You know how to hack?
Would I be here if I did?
I'd have done it already.
That's a crime.
Whatever.
I just need to be friends
with someone who can.
WINNER OF THE 35TH NATIONAL
COLLEGE ANTI-HACKING COMPETITION
Ye-won, do you want to do it?
Ye-won has a huge ego
and likes to show off.
She also likes a challenge.
She'd be less wary of you
who's a D than me who's a C.
We just need to find something
to persuade her.
Hey, Ye-won.
New laptop?
Looks nice.
-Is it a MacBook Pro?
-You know a lot about MacBooks?
I just know that it's expensive.
If you get the best graphic
card and memory
it's well over $10,000, isn't it?
That's the Mac Pro, right?
That's the new one
I have at home.
See you later in class.
Yeah, bye.
MACBOOK PRO
2023 MACBOOK PRO 16 INCH
LOWEST PRICE $4,840
YOON YE-WON
FATHER - RUNS YOON TOAST
MOTHER - HOUSEWIFE
HAS A STRONG DESIRE TO BE
RECOGNIZED AND HATES TO LOSE...
TENDS TO COMPLY
WHEN IT'S TO HER BENEFIT
Tends to comply
when it's to her benefit?
I just need to keep
an eye on her?
We're doomed.
PYRAMID GAME